{"prompt": "### 474 - 325 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 409 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 241 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 432 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 263 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 210 = answer{", "answer": 230}
{"prompt": "### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 17 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 402 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 450 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 249 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 236 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 441 = answer{", "answer": 42}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 460 = answer{-392} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 138 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{", "answer": 311}
{"prompt": "### 0 - 260 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 277 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 280 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{", "answer": -5}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 481 = answer{-387} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 469 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 318 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{", "answer": 150}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 147 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 191 = answer{85} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 326 = answer{", "answer": -149}
{"prompt": "### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 439 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 318 = answer{", "answer": 35}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 454 - 483 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 214 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 208 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 133 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 280 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 174 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{", "answer": 185}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 3 = answer{502} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 87 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 149 = answer{299} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 203 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 153 = answer{", "answer": -123}
{"prompt": "### 393 - 239 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 13 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 187 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{", "answer": -14}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 169 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 128 = answer{180} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 455 = answer{", "answer": -248}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 438 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 342 = answer{", "answer": 15}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 142 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 441 = answer{", "answer": -89}
{"prompt": "### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 496 = answer{-210} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{", "answer": -56}
{"prompt": "### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 481 = answer{-387} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 281 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 280}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -384}
{"prompt": "### 26 - 500 = answer{-474} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 177 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{489} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 281 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 468 = answer{", "answer": -116}
{"prompt": "### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 460 = answer{-425} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 81}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 511 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 375 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 431 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 105}
{"prompt": "### 69 - 349 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 450 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 74 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 311 = answer{", "answer": -22}
{"prompt": "### 63 - 259 = answer{-196} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{", "answer": -394}
{"prompt": "### 99 - 163 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 11 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 28 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 293 = answer{", "answer": -125}
{"prompt": "### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 197 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 159 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 396 = answer{", "answer": -126}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -151}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 183 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 312 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 221 = answer{", "answer": -56}
{"prompt": "### 353 - 318 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{-285} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 242 = answer{", "answer": -195}
{"prompt": "### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 352 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 71 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 216 = answer{", "answer": -211}
{"prompt": "### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 61 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 446 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 466 - 304 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -187}
{"prompt": "### 69 - 349 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 23 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 368 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 277 = answer{", "answer": 62}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 374 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 119 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 71 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 111 - 43 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 153 = answer{312} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{", "answer": 310}
{"prompt": "### 141 - 94 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 72 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 292 = answer{", "answer": -44}
{"prompt": "### 519 - 1 = answer{518} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 520 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{", "answer": 99}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 503 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 166 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 463 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 466 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{", "answer": 93}
{"prompt": "### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 354 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 142 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 484 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 97 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 80 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 365 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 401 = answer{", "answer": 44}
{"prompt": "### 373 - 282 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 378 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 198 = answer{", "answer": 26}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 25 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 472 = answer{17} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 514}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 194 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 112 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 69 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 383 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 482 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 313 = answer{", "answer": -150}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 14 = answer{263} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 443 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -280}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 41 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 319}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 435 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 458 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 233 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 132}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 511 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 71 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 375 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 502 = answer{", "answer": -389}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 191 = answer{85} ### <eop>\n### 386 - 82 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 482}
{"prompt": "### 474 - 364 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 395 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 224 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 105 = answer{", "answer": -89}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 152 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 353 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 190 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -95}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 442 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 139 = answer{260} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 183 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 244}
{"prompt": "### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 421 = answer{-385} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{", "answer": 338}
{"prompt": "### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 314 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 424 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{", "answer": 405}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 279 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 423 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 152 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 361 = answer{", "answer": -198}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 60 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 407 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 472 = answer{", "answer": -304}
{"prompt": "### 85 - 9 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 282 = answer{", "answer": 91}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 70 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 453 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{", "answer": -126}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 25 - 110 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 307 = answer{", "answer": -130}
{"prompt": "### 141 - 65 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 263 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -355}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 469 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{", "answer": -311}
{"prompt": "### 401 - 218 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 324 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 26 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 232 - 136 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 69 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 218 = answer{", "answer": 169}
{"prompt": "### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 461 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 113 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 18 = answer{", "answer": 472}
{"prompt": "### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 501 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 335 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 68 = answer{", "answer": 89}
{"prompt": "### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 40 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 277 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 229 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 129}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 450 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 27 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 61 = answer{13} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 453 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 476 = answer{", "answer": -17}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 462 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 116}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 109 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 217 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 9 = answer{", "answer": 52}
{"prompt": "### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 233 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 233 = answer{", "answer": -43}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 487 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 392 = answer{", "answer": -343}
{"prompt": "### 53 - 318 = answer{-265} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 370 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 361 = answer{", "answer": -347}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 237 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 272 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 209 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 233 - 370 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 219 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 343 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 446 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{", "answer": 291}
{"prompt": "### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 218 = answer{", "answer": 138}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 264 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 83 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{", "answer": 164}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 405 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 295 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 228 = answer{", "answer": 203}
{"prompt": "### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 213 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 204 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 282 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{", "answer": 239}
{"prompt": "### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 47 = answer{", "answer": 42}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 476 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 206 = answer{293} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{", "answer": 51}
{"prompt": "### 224 - 198 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 340 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 98 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 313 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{", "answer": -71}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 460 = answer{-425} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 159 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 260 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{", "answer": 77}
{"prompt": "### 400 - 358 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 249 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 120 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{", "answer": 65}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 97 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 456 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 518 = answer{-477} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{", "answer": 267}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 203 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 252 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 456 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 191 = answer{85} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 223 = answer{", "answer": -206}
{"prompt": "### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 338 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 287 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 91 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 168 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 14 = answer{429} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 174 - 411 = answer{-237} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 242 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{", "answer": 129}
{"prompt": "### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{240} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 13}
{"prompt": "### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 69 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 104 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 188 = answer{", "answer": -102}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 198 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 373 = answer{", "answer": -367}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 281 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 297 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 313 = answer{", "answer": -127}
{"prompt": "### 254 - 60 = answer{194} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 161 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 22 = answer{", "answer": 56}
{"prompt": "### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 113 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 442 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 154 = answer{", "answer": 253}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 423 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 138 - 203 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 128 = answer{", "answer": 215}
{"prompt": "### 272 - 61 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 11 - 72 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 149 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 338 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 172 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 466 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 349 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 30 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 138}
{"prompt": "### 304 - 392 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 224 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 127 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 324 = answer{", "answer": -70}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 385 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 59 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 183 = answer{", "answer": -63}
{"prompt": "### 436 - 422 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 297 = answer{-241} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 373 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{", "answer": -441}
{"prompt": "### 332 - 108 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 72 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 287 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 35 = answer{", "answer": 148}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 446 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 462 - 255 = answer{207} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 258 = answer{", "answer": 60}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 278 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 170 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 214 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 261 = answer{", "answer": 161}
{"prompt": "### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 43 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 375 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 218 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{", "answer": -321}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 325 = answer{-245} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 49 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 199 = answer{268} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 394 = answer{", "answer": -207}
{"prompt": "### 4 - 32 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 26 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 61 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 111 = answer{", "answer": -93}
{"prompt": "### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -118}
{"prompt": "### 245 - 274 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 29 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 474 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{", "answer": -273}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 503 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 418 = answer{", "answer": -240}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 438 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 113 = answer{", "answer": 10}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 40 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 126 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 144 = answer{-134} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{", "answer": 341}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 210}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 119 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 243 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 72 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 112 = answer{", "answer": 159}
{"prompt": "### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 464 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 110 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 7 = answer{", "answer": 134}
{"prompt": "### 499 - 206 = answer{293} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 388 = answer{", "answer": 31}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 14 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 204 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 266 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 394 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{", "answer": 103}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 3 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{", "answer": -173}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 336 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 298 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{", "answer": 242}
{"prompt": "### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 276 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 492 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 437 = answer{", "answer": -18}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 444 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 454 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{", "answer": -47}
{"prompt": "### 82 - 118 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 395}
{"prompt": "### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 465 = answer{-326} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{", "answer": 258}
{"prompt": "### 412 - 448 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 133 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 314 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 393 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 74 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 285 = answer{-245} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 118 = answer{", "answer": 141}
{"prompt": "### 346 - 22 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 243 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{", "answer": 105}
{"prompt": "### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -399}
{"prompt": "### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 210 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{", "answer": -153}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 360 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 310 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 435 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 189 = answer{", "answer": 177}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 21 = answer{", "answer": 455}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 375 = answer{", "answer": -366}
{"prompt": "### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 196 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 263 = answer{", "answer": 60}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 375 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{-285} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 59 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 387 = answer{", "answer": -314}
{"prompt": "### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 414 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{", "answer": -264}
{"prompt": "### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 375 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 70 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -79}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 395 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 453 = answer{", "answer": -98}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 209 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 428 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 130 = answer{", "answer": 106}
{"prompt": "### 223 - 501 = answer{-278} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 432 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 391 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{", "answer": -84}
{"prompt": "### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 435 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 394 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 434 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 144 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{", "answer": 191}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 411 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 143 = answer{302} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{", "answer": -90}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 152 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 204 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 350 = answer{", "answer": -272}
{"prompt": "### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 209 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 18}
{"prompt": "### 129 - 214 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -99}
{"prompt": "### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 463 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 115 = answer{", "answer": 247}
{"prompt": "### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 8 = answer{478} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 219 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 260 = answer{", "answer": 128}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 92 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 267 = answer{12} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 215 = answer{", "answer": 89}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 257 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 264 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 418}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 482 - 436 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 210 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 180 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 51 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 154 = answer{", "answer": 47}
{"prompt": "### 29 - 217 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 364 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 211}
{"prompt": "### 286 - 496 = answer{-210} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 485 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 454 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 143 = answer{302} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 368}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 246 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 407 = answer{-391} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{", "answer": -108}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 453 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 126 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{240} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 191 = answer{85} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 502 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{", "answer": -127}
{"prompt": "### 326 - 472 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 332 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 249 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 144 = answer{", "answer": -134}
{"prompt": "### 357 - 342 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 31 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 443 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 418 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 279 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -374}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 77 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 334 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{", "answer": 168}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 85 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 193 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 102 - 405 = answer{", "answer": -303}
{"prompt": "### 237 - 180 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 31 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 195 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 110 = answer{", "answer": 173}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 0 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 276 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 305}
{"prompt": "### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 437 = answer{", "answer": -400}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 61 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{", "answer": 29}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 313 = answer{-150} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 193 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 438 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{", "answer": -126}
{"prompt": "### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 485 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 450 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 515 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 175 = answer{", "answer": 333}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 213 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 314 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 133 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 489 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 446 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 59 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 150 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 368 = answer{", "answer": 59}
{"prompt": "### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 27 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 183 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{", "answer": 32}
{"prompt": "### 510 - 220 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 457 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 297 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 426 = answer{", "answer": -93}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 281 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 275 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{", "answer": 0}
{"prompt": "### 142 - 168 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 48 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 391 = answer{", "answer": -226}
{"prompt": "### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 385 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 224 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{", "answer": 164}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 1 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 10 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 243 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 109 = answer{", "answer": 399}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 439 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 218 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 423 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 116 = answer{", "answer": 48}
{"prompt": "### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 120 = answer{236} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 150 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 179}
{"prompt": "### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 398 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{", "answer": -94}
{"prompt": "### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 92 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 373}
{"prompt": "### 391 - 375 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 29 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 99 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 445 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{", "answer": 122}
{"prompt": "### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -152}
{"prompt": "### 132 - 0 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 411 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{308} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 57 = answer{", "answer": 183}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 119 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 463 = answer{", "answer": -42}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{-292} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 442 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{", "answer": -483}
{"prompt": "### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 38 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{", "answer": -207}
{"prompt": "### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 95 = answer{", "answer": 145}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 360 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 108 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 117 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{", "answer": 96}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 76 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 243 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 483 = answer{-349} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 309 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 349 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 309 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{", "answer": 62}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 53 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 120 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 291 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{", "answer": 89}
{"prompt": "### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 117 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 498 = answer{", "answer": -404}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 465 = answer{-326} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{", "answer": 1}
{"prompt": "### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 108 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 14 = answer{429} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{", "answer": -328}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 239 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 298 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 240 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 110 = answer{", "answer": 204}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 203 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 83 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 366 = answer{", "answer": -154}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 153 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 483 = answer{", "answer": -349}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 323 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 153 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 498 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 71 = answer{", "answer": 362}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 14 = answer{158} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 25 = answer{484} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 150 = answer{", "answer": 142}
{"prompt": "### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 229 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 50 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 272 = answer{", "answer": -14}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 106 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 69 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{", "answer": 365}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 167 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -192}
{"prompt": "### 464 - 329 = answer{135} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{", "answer": -76}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 372 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 192 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 50 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 295 = answer{", "answer": -252}
{"prompt": "### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{", "answer": -321}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 387 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 236 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 116 = answer{231} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{", "answer": -252}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 175 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 395 = answer{", "answer": -204}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{308} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{", "answer": 125}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 365 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 439 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 114 = answer{", "answer": 159}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 72 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 79 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{", "answer": -315}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 324 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 323 = answer{151} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{", "answer": -345}
{"prompt": "### 168 - 472 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 281 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 313 = answer{", "answer": -40}
{"prompt": "### 25 - 110 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 87 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 136 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 253 = answer{", "answer": 57}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 411 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 29 = answer{487} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 348 = answer{", "answer": -115}
{"prompt": "### 172 - 14 = answer{158} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 158 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 195 = answer{", "answer": 11}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 55 = answer{391} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 71 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 128 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 9 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 447 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 483 = answer{", "answer": -267}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 161 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 10 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 425 = answer{", "answer": 74}
{"prompt": "### 96 - 409 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 384 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 360 = answer{", "answer": -118}
{"prompt": "### 190 - 233 = answer{-43} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 103 - 258 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 389 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{", "answer": 297}
{"prompt": "### 22 - 188 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 159 = answer{177} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 227 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 168 = answer{", "answer": -26}
{"prompt": "### 380 - 62 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 78 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 428 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 146 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 178 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 404 = answer{", "answer": 11}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 148 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 150 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 208 = answer{", "answer": 244}
{"prompt": "### 109 - 28 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 468 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 169 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 103 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 77 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 21 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 196 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{", "answer": 304}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 59 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 394 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 486 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 89 = answer{", "answer": -66}
{"prompt": "### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 1 = answer{518} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 95 = answer{145} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 392 = answer{", "answer": -88}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 364 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{", "answer": -282}
{"prompt": "### 119 - 288 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 157 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 434 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 207 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 152 - 167 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 283 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 10 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 179 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 50 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 476 = answer{", "answer": -175}
{"prompt": "### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 314 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 387 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 367 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 288 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 275 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 108 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 178 = answer{", "answer": 31}
{"prompt": "### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 113 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 501 = answer{", "answer": -366}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 69 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 59 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{", "answer": 275}
{"prompt": "### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 368 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 428 = answer{", "answer": 32}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 127 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 354 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -192}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 213 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 290 = answer{", "answer": -276}
{"prompt": "### 499 - 386 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 438 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 266 = answer{156} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 248 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{", "answer": -53}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 43 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 121 = answer{", "answer": -3}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 52 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 401 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 183 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 249 = answer{", "answer": 96}
{"prompt": "### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 243 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 197 = answer{", "answer": 143}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 515 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 297 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 120 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{", "answer": -142}
{"prompt": "### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 411 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 17 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 415 = answer{-10} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{", "answer": 330}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 139 = answer{260} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 149 = answer{", "answer": 299}
{"prompt": "### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 284 = answer{-228} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 235 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 142}
{"prompt": "### 308 - 128 = answer{180} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 482 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 300}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 209 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 472 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 298 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 141 - 65 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 428 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 400 = answer{", "answer": -250}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 195 = answer{", "answer": 257}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 27 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 249 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{", "answer": -105}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 463 = answer{", "answer": -171}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 276 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 345}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 145 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 419 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{", "answer": 346}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 284 - 381 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 350 = answer{-317} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{", "answer": -92}
{"prompt": "### 29 - 217 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 38 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 168 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 237 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 179 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 329 = answer{", "answer": 135}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 183 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 379 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 442 = answer{-439} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 420 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 418 - 402 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 13 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 196 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 471 = answer{", "answer": -455}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 411 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 378 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 118 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -445}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 77 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -494}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 65 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 136 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 506 = answer{-373} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 434 = answer{", "answer": -54}
{"prompt": "### 482 - 436 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 64 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 438}
{"prompt": "### 65 - 241 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 493 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 400 = answer{-351} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 339 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 324 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 368 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 507 = answer{-418} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{", "answer": -273}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 304 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 117 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 47 = answer{", "answer": 386}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 361 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 366 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 380 = answer{", "answer": -121}
{"prompt": "### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 120 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 349 = answer{", "answer": -60}
{"prompt": "### 96 - 365 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 5 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 175 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 32 = answer{", "answer": 247}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 59 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 443 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 410}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 14 = answer{158} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 147}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 30 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 159 = answer{", "answer": 354}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 149 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 3 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 197 = answer{", "answer": 238}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 65 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 304 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 50 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 99 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{", "answer": -128}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{", "answer": 31}
{"prompt": "### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 344 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 251 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 29 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 354 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 97 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 129 = answer{269} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -505}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 409 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 357 - 370 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -429}
{"prompt": "### 34 - 268 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 364 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 264 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 419 = answer{", "answer": -174}
{"prompt": "### 65 - 226 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{", "answer": 465}
{"prompt": "### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 322 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 269 - 146 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 336 = answer{", "answer": -268}
{"prompt": "### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 370 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 79 = answer{", "answer": 132}
{"prompt": "### 63 - 235 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 485 - 174 = answer{", "answer": 311}
{"prompt": "### 172 - 14 = answer{158} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 129 = answer{269} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 384}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 237 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 45 - 6 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 344 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 94 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 457 - 2 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -484}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 284 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 277 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 281 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -307}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 323 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 2 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 95 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 51 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 53 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 438 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -27}
{"prompt": "### 474 - 209 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 280 = answer{", "answer": -179}
{"prompt": "### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 508 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 349 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{", "answer": -87}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 31 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 278 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 229 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 323 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{", "answer": -143}
{"prompt": "### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 274 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 126 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 279 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -233}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 246 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 462 - 255 = answer{207} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 3 - 442 = answer{-439} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 415 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 414 = answer{-199} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{", "answer": -230}
{"prompt": "### 478 - 88 = answer{390} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 379 = answer{", "answer": -195}
{"prompt": "### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 56 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 105 = answer{", "answer": 266}
{"prompt": "### 101 - 280 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 404 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 146 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 335 = answer{", "answer": -100}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 71 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 437 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{", "answer": -227}
{"prompt": "### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 358 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 418 = answer{-275} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 284 = answer{", "answer": 8}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 243 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 257 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 206 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 80 = answer{384} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 224 = answer{", "answer": 68}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 353 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 437 = answer{-435} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 442 = answer{-439} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{", "answer": -100}
{"prompt": "### 56 - 297 = answer{-241} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 336 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 279 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 2 = answer{124} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 463 = answer{", "answer": -277}
{"prompt": "### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 67 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 442 = answer{", "answer": -141}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 366 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 25 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 78 = answer{", "answer": 298}
{"prompt": "### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 293 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 463 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 255 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 165 = answer{", "answer": 174}
{"prompt": "### 111 - 140 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 426 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 310}
{"prompt": "### 391 - 375 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 193 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 419 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -147}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 172 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 8 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 85 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{", "answer": -123}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 14 = answer{429} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 426 = answer{", "answer": -151}
{"prompt": "### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{", "answer": 175}
{"prompt": "### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 204 = answer{", "answer": -192}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 123 = answer{97} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 23 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 214 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 8 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{", "answer": 29}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 210 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 461 = answer{", "answer": -185}
{"prompt": "### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 506 = answer{-505} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 116 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 284 - 381 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 75 = answer{", "answer": 214}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 471 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 365 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 367 = answer{", "answer": -232}
{"prompt": "### 126 - 25 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 373 = answer{-367} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -95}
{"prompt": "### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 92 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 439 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 158 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 38 = answer{", "answer": 359}
{"prompt": "### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 370 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 20 = answer{353} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 18}
{"prompt": "### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 320 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 236}
{"prompt": "### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 136 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 483 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 130 = answer{", "answer": 272}
{"prompt": "### 192 - 67 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 401 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 198 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 72 = answer{", "answer": 327}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 83 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 389 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 25 = answer{", "answer": 101}
{"prompt": "### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 275 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 287 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 334 = answer{", "answer": -248}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{", "answer": 92}
{"prompt": "### 127 - 103 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 115}
{"prompt": "### 107 - 420 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 80 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{-310} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 485 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 134 = answer{", "answer": 141}
{"prompt": "### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 20 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 95 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 273}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 360 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 20 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 317 = answer{", "answer": 80}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 270 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 36 = answer{", "answer": 168}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 55 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 443 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 257}
{"prompt": "### 395 - 0 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 146 = answer{", "answer": 174}
{"prompt": "### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{", "answer": -162}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 287 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 79 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{", "answer": -8}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 117 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 514 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 515 = answer{", "answer": -359}
{"prompt": "### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 218 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 171 - 337 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 29 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 8 = answer{", "answer": 478}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 416 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 33 = answer{", "answer": 472}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 450 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 31 = answer{377} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -104}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 237 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 128 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{406} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 46}
{"prompt": "### 461 - 490 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 405 = answer{", "answer": -96}
{"prompt": "### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 463 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 365 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 428 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 158 = answer{", "answer": 66}
{"prompt": "### 411 - 120 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 181 = answer{218} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 241 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 35 = answer{133} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -72}
{"prompt": "### 28 - 21 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{206} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 10 = answer{", "answer": 438}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 201 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 279 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 301 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 402 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 361}
{"prompt": "### 36 - 421 = answer{-385} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 106 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 269 - 146 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 73 = answer{", "answer": 163}
{"prompt": "### 373 - 20 = answer{353} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 280 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 498 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 353 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{", "answer": -78}
{"prompt": "### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 21 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 8 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 150 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{", "answer": -214}
{"prompt": "### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 389 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 38 = answer{359} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 69 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{", "answer": 435}
{"prompt": "### 380 - 446 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 248 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 503 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 23 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 472 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 27 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{", "answer": -383}
{"prompt": "### 174 - 59 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 460 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 224 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 156 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 382 = answer{", "answer": -297}
{"prompt": "### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 0 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 487 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 297 = answer{", "answer": -241}
{"prompt": "### 105 - 143 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 320 = answer{", "answer": -124}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 62 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 107 = answer{", "answer": 241}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 171 - 337 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 360}
{"prompt": "### 398 - 122 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 274 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{", "answer": -113}
{"prompt": "### 356 - 218 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 395 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 250 - 42 = answer{", "answer": 208}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 509 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 464 = answer{-463} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 432 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 453 = answer{", "answer": -182}
{"prompt": "### 420 - 325 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{308} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{", "answer": 105}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 72 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 236 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 164 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 11 = answer{", "answer": 482}
{"prompt": "### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 57 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 95 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 439 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 376 - 89 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 313 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -260}
{"prompt": "### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 9 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 420 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 150 = answer{", "answer": 248}
{"prompt": "### 64 - 515 = answer{-451} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 287 = answer{", "answer": -56}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 179 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 117 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 119 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 284 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 72 = answer{", "answer": 4}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 28 = answer{468} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 453 = answer{", "answer": -110}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 368 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 326 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 453 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 66}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 153 = answer{312} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 301 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 29 = answer{", "answer": 211}
{"prompt": "### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 113 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 89 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 364 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 322 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 3 = answer{", "answer": 216}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{", "answer": 117}
{"prompt": "### 349 - 267 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 349 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 76 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 267 = answer{", "answer": 252}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 425 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 466 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 289 = answer{", "answer": 116}
{"prompt": "### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 287 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 465 = answer{", "answer": -73}
{"prompt": "### 142 - 196 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 149 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 185 = answer{", "answer": 176}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 27 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 498 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 439 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 89 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 472 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 113 = answer{", "answer": -9}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 439 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 249 = answer{", "answer": -226}
{"prompt": "### 164 - 116 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 189 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 278 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 118 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 278 = answer{", "answer": 68}
{"prompt": "### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 116 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 100 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 209 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 438 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 123 = answer{97} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 251 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 70 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 398 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 369 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{", "answer": -223}
{"prompt": "### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 365 = answer{-158} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 150 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{370} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 169 = answer{", "answer": 10}
{"prompt": "### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 11 - 72 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{", "answer": -208}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 3 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 410 - 64 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{", "answer": -271}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 105 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 352 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 6 = answer{514} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 365 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 494 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{", "answer": 26}
{"prompt": "### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 481 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 287 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 177 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 19 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{", "answer": 257}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 295 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 142 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 298 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 29 = answer{", "answer": 487}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 503 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 161 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 175 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 446 = answer{", "answer": -124}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 31 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 42 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 120 = answer{236} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{256} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{", "answer": -19}
{"prompt": "### 402 - 130 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 68 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 220 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 177 = answer{", "answer": 175}
{"prompt": "### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 3 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 502 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 21 = answer{", "answer": 7}
{"prompt": "### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 178 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 223 = answer{-20} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 292 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 466 = answer{", "answer": -353}
{"prompt": "### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 425 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 17 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 365 = answer{-158} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 432 = answer{", "answer": -41}
{"prompt": "### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{", "answer": 138}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 23 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 228 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 369 = answer{", "answer": -327}
{"prompt": "### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 367 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 259 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 385}
{"prompt": "### 140 - 97 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 376 = answer{121} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 447 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 163 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 201 - 278 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 126 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 183 = answer{", "answer": -115}
{"prompt": "### 274 - 260 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 375 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 280 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 358 = answer{", "answer": -251}
{"prompt": "### 218 - 520 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 70 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 152 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 106 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -363}
{"prompt": "### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 226 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 193 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{", "answer": 52}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 312 = answer{", "answer": -97}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 361 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 142 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 205 = answer{", "answer": 228}
{"prompt": "### 509 - 25 = answer{484} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 506 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 511 = answer{", "answer": -156}
{"prompt": "### 150 - 90 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 259 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 225 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 313 = answer{", "answer": 200}
{"prompt": "### 309 - 251 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 364 = answer{", "answer": 110}
{"prompt": "### 174 - 349 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 111 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{", "answer": 120}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 238 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 426}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 225 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 408 = answer{-378} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 215 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 425 = answer{", "answer": -201}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 101 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 198 = answer{", "answer": 60}
{"prompt": "### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 304 = answer{", "answer": -28}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 27 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{", "answer": 78}
{"prompt": "### 183 - 164 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 77 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 231 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 295 = answer{", "answer": -145}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 70 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 147 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 123 = answer{", "answer": -4}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 53 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -96}
{"prompt": "### 129 - 277 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 288 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 152 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 281 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 100 = answer{", "answer": 225}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{256} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 446 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 255 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 17 = answer{", "answer": 230}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 116 = answer{231} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 373 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 255 = answer{", "answer": -206}
{"prompt": "### 82 - 118 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 514 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 224 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 462 - 255 = answer{207} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 128 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 44 = answer{", "answer": 334}
{"prompt": "### 483 - 275 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 116 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{", "answer": -169}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 238 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 94 = answer{", "answer": 113}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 161 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 386 - 82 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 242 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{", "answer": -330}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 408 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{", "answer": 265}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 252 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 178 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 358 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 469 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 26 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 160 = answer{", "answer": 170}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 514 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 179 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 79 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{", "answer": -269}
{"prompt": "### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 481 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{", "answer": 423}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 495 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 183 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{", "answer": -49}
{"prompt": "### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 492 = answer{-296} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 284 = answer{", "answer": 58}
{"prompt": "### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 2 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -425}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 47 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{", "answer": -68}
{"prompt": "### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 179 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 237 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 235}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 137 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 280 = answer{", "answer": -34}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 358 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 96}
{"prompt": "### 356 - 218 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 312 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 404 = answer{", "answer": -7}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 98 = answer{182} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 307 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 447 = answer{", "answer": 21}
{"prompt": "### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 438 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 496 = answer{", "answer": -210}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 269 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 130 = answer{106} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 99 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -331}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 41 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 114 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -391}
{"prompt": "### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 235 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 293 = answer{", "answer": 5}
{"prompt": "### 262 - 20 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 154 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 265 = answer{", "answer": -63}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 91 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 99 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 163 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 120 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{", "answer": -49}
{"prompt": "### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 105 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{", "answer": 197}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 14 = answer{158} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 53 = answer{", "answer": 167}
{"prompt": "### 195 - 36 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 3 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 496 = answer{-210} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 298 = answer{", "answer": -66}
{"prompt": "### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 72 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 12 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 68 = answer{", "answer": 392}
{"prompt": "### 308 - 385 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 54 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 346 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 9 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 231 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 264 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 278 = answer{", "answer": -1}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 120 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 402 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 233 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 68 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 241 = answer{", "answer": -176}
{"prompt": "### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 163 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 510 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 456 = answer{", "answer": 36}
{"prompt": "### 177 - 307 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 460 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{", "answer": -154}
{"prompt": "### 249 - 440 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 166 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 389 = answer{", "answer": -200}
{"prompt": "### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 442 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 2 = answer{", "answer": 225}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 53 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 385}
{"prompt": "### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 358 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 298 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 238 = answer{", "answer": 23}
{"prompt": "### 279 - 32 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 9 = answer{102} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 327 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 140 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 285 = answer{", "answer": -245}
{"prompt": "### 166 - 164 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 10 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 402 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 7 = answer{228} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 399 = answer{", "answer": 118}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 344 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{", "answer": -383}
{"prompt": "### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 204 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 238 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 358 = answer{", "answer": -234}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 46 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 180 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 510 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 231 = answer{", "answer": 159}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 177 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 318 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 121 = answer{", "answer": 39}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 135 = answer{171} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 26 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 116 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{", "answer": 442}
{"prompt": "### 297 - 224 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 419 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{", "answer": 220}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 18 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 301 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 327 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 85 = answer{", "answer": 250}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 134 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 486 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 455 - 471 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 262 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 127 = answer{", "answer": 376}
{"prompt": "### 58 - 320 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 312 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 387}
{"prompt": "### 150 - 400 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{", "answer": -152}
{"prompt": "### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 40 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 394}
{"prompt": "### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 262 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 337 - 368 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 233 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 230 = answer{", "answer": -139}
{"prompt": "### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 377 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 277 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 386 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 258 = answer{", "answer": -95}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 514 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 195}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 469 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 134 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 344 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 481 = answer{", "answer": -149}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 61 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{", "answer": -75}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 170 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 490 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 511 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 29 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{", "answer": 30}
{"prompt": "### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 16 = answer{352} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 437 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 409 = answer{", "answer": 25}
{"prompt": "### 289 - 311 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 435 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 164 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 320 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -54}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 261 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 25 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 212 - 27 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 358 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 280 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 483 = answer{-349} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 30 = answer{", "answer": 258}
{"prompt": "### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 36 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 22 = answer{", "answer": 324}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 237 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 198 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{489} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 124 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 131 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 252 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 75 = answer{443} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 160 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 203}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 213 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 520 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 190 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 280 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 282 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 386 - 82 = answer{", "answer": 304}
{"prompt": "### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{240} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 339 = answer{", "answer": -268}
{"prompt": "### 310 - 430 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 291 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 316 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 108 = answer{", "answer": 224}
{"prompt": "### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 100 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{", "answer": 338}
{"prompt": "### 393 - 357 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 356 - 218 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 275 = answer{", "answer": 168}
{"prompt": "### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 297 = answer{-241} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 2 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 270 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 188 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 420 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 316 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{", "answer": -342}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 410 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 156 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 166 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 472 - 196 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 227 = answer{", "answer": 131}
{"prompt": "### 252 - 259 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 80 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 498 - 385 = answer{", "answer": 113}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 78 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 39 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 249 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 244 = answer{", "answer": 52}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 252 - 259 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 153 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{", "answer": -40}
{"prompt": "### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 88 = answer{", "answer": 390}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 306 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{", "answer": -309}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 3 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 490 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 258 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 501 = answer{-278} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 406 = answer{", "answer": -247}
{"prompt": "### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 37 = answer{", "answer": 394}
{"prompt": "### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 269 - 146 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 200 = answer{", "answer": 273}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 284 = answer{-228} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 306 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 312 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 206 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 134 - 483 = answer{-349} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 68 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 492 = answer{-296} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 175 = answer{", "answer": 112}
{"prompt": "### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 154 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 77 = answer{", "answer": 407}
{"prompt": "### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 280 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 295 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 163 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 251 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{", "answer": 219}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 46 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 36 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 30 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 142 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 377 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 266 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 25 = answer{", "answer": 202}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 464 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 183 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 426 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 149 = answer{", "answer": 81}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 409 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 418 = answer{-275} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{", "answer": -93}
{"prompt": "### 43 - 454 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 472 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 61 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 343 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 177 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 220 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 322 = answer{", "answer": 55}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{", "answer": -281}
{"prompt": "### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 193 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 36 = answer{", "answer": 398}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 519 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 29 = answer{487} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 422 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{", "answer": 170}
{"prompt": "### 471 - 152 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 113 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 241 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 275 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 276 - 455 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 422 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 352 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 131 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 476 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 196 = answer{", "answer": -154}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 482 - 436 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 293 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 442 = answer{-439} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 174 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 139 = answer{260} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 214 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{", "answer": 381}
{"prompt": "### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 10 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 189 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{", "answer": 33}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 226 = answer{-30} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 492 = answer{-296} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{", "answer": 7}
{"prompt": "### 457 - 152 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 408 = answer{-378} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 327 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 153 = answer{", "answer": 312}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 299 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 283 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 401 - 218 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 450 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{", "answer": -47}
{"prompt": "### 177 - 326 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 255 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 2 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 202 = answer{", "answer": -26}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 437 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 187 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{-310} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 360 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 414 = answer{", "answer": -381}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 27 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 299 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 14 = answer{263} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{", "answer": -310}
{"prompt": "### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 204 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 125 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 53 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 239 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 324 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 117 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 502 = answer{-295} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 507 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 338 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 179 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 300 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 36 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 17 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 267 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 307 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 1 = answer{", "answer": 518}
{"prompt": "### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 342 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 374 = answer{", "answer": 68}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 29 = answer{", "answer": 386}
{"prompt": "### 350 - 298 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 102 - 405 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 82 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 35 = answer{", "answer": 47}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 501 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 275 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{", "answer": -53}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 335 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 377 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 78 = answer{", "answer": 284}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 263 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 372 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{", "answer": 114}
{"prompt": "### 101 - 280 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{", "answer": -110}
{"prompt": "### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 132 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{", "answer": 35}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 170 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 285 = answer{-245} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 471 = answer{", "answer": -302}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 260 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 61 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{", "answer": -374}
{"prompt": "### 358 - 227 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 450 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{", "answer": -248}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 244 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 193 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 1 = answer{", "answer": 19}
{"prompt": "### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 492 = answer{", "answer": -296}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 393 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 269 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{", "answer": 61}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -346}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 460 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 249 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 119 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 294 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 320 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 364 = answer{", "answer": 101}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 297 = answer{-241} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 16 = answer{", "answer": 352}
{"prompt": "### 464 - 80 = answer{384} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 206 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 211 = answer{", "answer": -101}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 515 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 1 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 439 = answer{", "answer": -73}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{", "answer": -49}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 199 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 367 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 314 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 59 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -237}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 290 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 229 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 91 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 212 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 199 = answer{", "answer": 268}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 279 = answer{", "answer": -171}
{"prompt": "### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 260 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 156 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 342 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{", "answer": 69}
{"prompt": "### 123 - 85 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 293 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 190 = answer{-107} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 229 = answer{", "answer": 192}
{"prompt": "### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 344 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 252 - 259 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 313 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 362 = answer{", "answer": 9}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{", "answer": -318}
{"prompt": "### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 300 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 150 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 278 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 270}
{"prompt": "### 86 - 334 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 102 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 281 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 175 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 472 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 8 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 132 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 222 - 445 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 241 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 181 = answer{", "answer": 7}
{"prompt": "### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 307 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 273 = answer{", "answer": -12}
{"prompt": "### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 344 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 113 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{", "answer": -262}
{"prompt": "### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 198 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 23 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{", "answer": 23}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 5 = answer{515} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 11 = answer{189} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 338 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{", "answer": 8}
{"prompt": "### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 169 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{", "answer": 8}
{"prompt": "### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 228 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 353 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -120}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{-285} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 163 = answer{", "answer": 191}
{"prompt": "### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{452} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 284 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 279 = answer{", "answer": 114}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 31 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 377 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{", "answer": 254}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 338 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 268 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{", "answer": -140}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 388 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 446 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 26 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 179 = answer{", "answer": 54}
{"prompt": "### 22 - 188 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 128 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{", "answer": -22}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 91 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 22 - 188 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 292 = answer{", "answer": 200}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{", "answer": -332}
{"prompt": "### 17 - 223 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 43 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 293 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 294 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 107 = answer{241} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 145 = answer{", "answer": -117}
{"prompt": "### 191 - 3 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 391 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 146 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 447 = answer{", "answer": 40}
{"prompt": "### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 369 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 438 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{", "answer": 165}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{256} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 206 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 275 = answer{", "answer": -17}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 447 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 365 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{", "answer": 165}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 261 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 456 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 102 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 74 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{", "answer": 252}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 488 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 168 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 83 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 316 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{", "answer": 27}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 442 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 251 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 333 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 85 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 110 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 59 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{", "answer": 262}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 379 = answer{", "answer": -41}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 72 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 40 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 181 = answer{218} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 180 = answer{", "answer": 57}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 196 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{", "answer": 203}
{"prompt": "### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 494 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 89 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 486 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{", "answer": -169}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 507 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{", "answer": -229}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 324 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 46 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 344 = answer{", "answer": 3}
{"prompt": "### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 320 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 200 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 161}
{"prompt": "### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 115 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 472 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 355 = answer{", "answer": -301}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 61 = answer{13} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 130 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 460 = answer{-264} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 443 = answer{", "answer": -171}
{"prompt": "### 204 - 36 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 438 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 199 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 299 = answer{", "answer": -136}
{"prompt": "### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 327 = answer{", "answer": -126}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 345 = answer{", "answer": 94}
{"prompt": "### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 77 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{", "answer": -68}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 407 = answer{-391} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 167 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 85 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 476 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 54 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 374 = answer{", "answer": -67}
{"prompt": "### 108 - 21 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 219 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 344 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 142 = answer{", "answer": -80}
{"prompt": "### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 519 = answer{", "answer": -116}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 67 = answer{433} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 124 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{", "answer": -82}
{"prompt": "### 23 - 249 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 12 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 76 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 482 = answer{", "answer": -173}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 147 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 206 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{", "answer": 409}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 253 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 441 = answer{", "answer": -106}
{"prompt": "### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 260 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 60 = answer{194} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 126 = answer{", "answer": 191}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 115 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 320 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{", "answer": 366}
{"prompt": "### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 514 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 413 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{", "answer": 454}
{"prompt": "### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 295 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 182 = answer{", "answer": -22}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 272 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 364 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 378 = answer{", "answer": -93}
{"prompt": "### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 116 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 379 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 456 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 253 - 100 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 67}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 453 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 393 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 87 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 340}
{"prompt": "### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 313 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 246 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 428 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 497 = answer{-220} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 344 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 124 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 316 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 441 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 323 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 68}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 246 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 172 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 13 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 178 = answer{", "answer": 87}
{"prompt": "### 63 - 259 = answer{-196} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 89 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 402 = answer{", "answer": -192}
{"prompt": "### 170 - 426 = answer{-256} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 437 = answer{-435} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 144 = answer{-134} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 335 = answer{-306} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{", "answer": 58}
{"prompt": "### 405 - 289 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 506 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 157 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 258 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{", "answer": 407}
{"prompt": "### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 75 = answer{214} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 107 = answer{241} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 356}
{"prompt": "### 51 - 237 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 397 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 153 = answer{", "answer": 9}
{"prompt": "### 254 - 213 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 284 = answer{-228} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 14 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 95 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 82 = answer{", "answer": 169}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 38 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 252 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 113 = answer{", "answer": 45}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{406} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 30 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 170 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 68 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 426 = answer{-256} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 33 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 299 = answer{", "answer": -261}
{"prompt": "### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 225 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 146 = answer{", "answer": 216}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 313 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 460 = answer{-425} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{", "answer": 72}
{"prompt": "### 468 - 447 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 107 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 305 = answer{", "answer": -191}
{"prompt": "### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 278 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 18 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{", "answer": -200}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 375 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 41 = answer{", "answer": 379}
{"prompt": "### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 509 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 462 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 30 = answer{", "answer": 328}
{"prompt": "### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 253 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{", "answer": -216}
{"prompt": "### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 290 = answer{", "answer": 197}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 429 - 39 = answer{390} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 250 = answer{209} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 430 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 156 = answer{", "answer": 304}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 496 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 132 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 107 = answer{", "answer": 306}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 20 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 187 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 335 = answer{", "answer": 22}
{"prompt": "### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 61 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 426 = answer{-256} ### <eop>\n### 253 - 100 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 142 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{", "answer": -270}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 216 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 237 = answer{", "answer": -186}
{"prompt": "### 34 - 119 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 35 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 236 = answer{", "answer": -49}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 510 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 443 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 466 = answer{", "answer": -320}
{"prompt": "### 123 - 430 = answer{-307} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 420 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 258 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{", "answer": 46}
{"prompt": "### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 72 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 496 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{", "answer": 272}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 396 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 77 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 69 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 92 = answer{", "answer": -72}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 126 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 0 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 38 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 509 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 132 - 247 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 280 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 231 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 490 = answer{", "answer": -98}
{"prompt": "### 376 - 78 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 392 = answer{-343} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 396 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -113}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 287 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 164 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 253 - 100 = answer{", "answer": 153}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 502 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 158 = answer{", "answer": 77}
{"prompt": "### 499 - 442 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 17 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 448 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 71}
{"prompt": "### 298 - 411 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 30 = answer{", "answer": 426}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 214 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 502 = answer{-295} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 97 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 6 = answer{", "answer": 26}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 65 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 108 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 260 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 344 = answer{", "answer": 70}
{"prompt": "### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 26 = answer{", "answer": 57}
{"prompt": "### 456 - 30 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 309 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 41}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 205 = answer{228} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 37}
{"prompt": "### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 257 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 445 = answer{", "answer": -79}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 113 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 389 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{", "answer": -21}
{"prompt": "### 93 - 500 = answer{-407} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{", "answer": 77}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 424 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{", "answer": 49}
{"prompt": "### 31 - 414 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 411 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{", "answer": 173}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 107 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 163 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{", "answer": 93}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 327 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 74 = answer{", "answer": 278}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 277 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 306 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 51 = answer{", "answer": 48}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 33 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 106 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 471 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 223 = answer{", "answer": -20}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 71 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 145 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 115 - 409 = answer{-294} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 115 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 224 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 519 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{370} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{470} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 139 = answer{", "answer": 260}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{308} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 490 = answer{-3} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 518 = answer{", "answer": -314}
{"prompt": "### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 239 - 31 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{", "answer": -128}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 133 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 515 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{", "answer": 175}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{", "answer": 104}
{"prompt": "### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 461 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 191 = answer{302} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{", "answer": -144}
{"prompt": "### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 412 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{", "answer": 169}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 229 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 305 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 90 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 281 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 377}
{"prompt": "### 413 - 107 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 515 = answer{", "answer": -214}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 252 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 374 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 152 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 408 = answer{", "answer": -152}
{"prompt": "### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 327 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 468 = answer{", "answer": -21}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 152 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 308 = answer{", "answer": 137}
{"prompt": "### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 196 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 43 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 259 = answer{", "answer": -18}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 265 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 20 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 2 = answer{124} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{", "answer": -270}
{"prompt": "### 11 - 72 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 209 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 349 = answer{", "answer": -175}
{"prompt": "### 378 - 456 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 5 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 417 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 444 = answer{", "answer": -293}
{"prompt": "### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 509 = answer{-495} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 488 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{", "answer": 277}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 120 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 279 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 25 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 172 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 38 = answer{", "answer": -7}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 486 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 213 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 446 = answer{", "answer": -434}
{"prompt": "### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 236 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 495 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{", "answer": -399}
{"prompt": "### 111 - 43 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 164 = answer{", "answer": -67}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 275 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 447 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 385 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 304 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 70 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{", "answer": -106}
{"prompt": "### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{-285} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 466 = answer{", "answer": -152}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 482 - 436 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 147 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 169 = answer{", "answer": 351}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 64 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 412 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -353}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 8 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 228 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 374 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{", "answer": -365}
{"prompt": "### 33 - 350 = answer{-317} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 360 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 202 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 375 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 89 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 270 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 220 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 463 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{256} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -186}
{"prompt": "### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 238 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 485 = answer{", "answer": -159}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 496 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 103 - 258 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 27 = answer{", "answer": 185}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 14 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 446 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{", "answer": 79}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 439 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 439 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{", "answer": -369}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 509 = answer{-495} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 75 = answer{443} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 61 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 175 = answer{", "answer": -107}
{"prompt": "### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 486 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 487 = answer{", "answer": -257}
{"prompt": "### 338 - 379 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 518 = answer{-477} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 38 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 121 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 159 = answer{", "answer": 205}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 503 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 243 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 224 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 378}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 228 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 376 = answer{121} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 138 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 121 = answer{", "answer": 37}
{"prompt": "### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 152 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 393 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 354 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 163 = answer{", "answer": 96}
{"prompt": "### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 283 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 486 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 372 = answer{", "answer": -135}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 50 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 225 = answer{", "answer": 82}
{"prompt": "### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 339 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 54 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 294 = answer{", "answer": -93}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 61 = answer{363} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{", "answer": 277}
{"prompt": "### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 437 = answer{-435} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 41 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 264 = answer{", "answer": -203}
{"prompt": "### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 282 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 476 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 161 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 443 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 214 = answer{", "answer": -162}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 275 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 45 - 6 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 91 = answer{", "answer": 351}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 94 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 119 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 393 = answer{", "answer": -376}
{"prompt": "### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 515 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 29 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 139 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 251 = answer{", "answer": 58}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 115 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 160 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{", "answer": 108}
{"prompt": "### 130 - 276 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 107 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{", "answer": 270}
{"prompt": "### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 413 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 138 - 203 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 484 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{-396} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 166 = answer{", "answer": 133}
{"prompt": "### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 138 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 274 = answer{", "answer": -255}
{"prompt": "### 418 - 483 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 31 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 326 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 31 = answer{377} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 142 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 471 = answer{", "answer": -156}
{"prompt": "### 270 - 396 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 323 = answer{", "answer": -207}
{"prompt": "### 460 - 68 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 295 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{", "answer": 188}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 343 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 150 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 166 = answer{133} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 193 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{", "answer": -171}
{"prompt": "### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 317 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 191 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 222 - 445 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 64 = answer{", "answer": 279}
{"prompt": "### 84 - 375 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 266 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{", "answer": 178}
{"prompt": "### 39 - 53 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 214 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 474 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 264 = answer{", "answer": -32}
{"prompt": "### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 249 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 212 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{", "answer": 193}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 111 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 369 = answer{", "answer": -123}
{"prompt": "### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 492 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 9 = answer{", "answer": 102}
{"prompt": "### 200 - 11 = answer{189} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 136 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{", "answer": 354}
{"prompt": "### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 51 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 50 = answer{", "answer": 215}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 249 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 305 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -137}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 156 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 212 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 46 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 55 = answer{391} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 65 - 241 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 59 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 2 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 169 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -407}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 102 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 30 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 374 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 132 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 361 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 155 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 80 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 128 = answer{", "answer": 243}
{"prompt": "### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 236 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -76}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 388 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 88 = answer{390} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 110 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 51 = answer{315} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 278 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 402 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 318 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 433 = answer{", "answer": -335}
{"prompt": "### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 364 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 89 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 231 = answer{", "answer": 99}
{"prompt": "### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 217 = answer{", "answer": -188}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 364 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 240 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 39 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 31 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{", "answer": -238}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 80 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 243 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 514 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{", "answer": 128}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 120 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 97 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 230 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 56 = answer{", "answer": 51}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 462 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 503 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 42 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 428 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 256 = answer{", "answer": -205}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 72 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 139 = answer{", "answer": 23}
{"prompt": "### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 275 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 340 = answer{", "answer": -78}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{", "answer": -327}
{"prompt": "### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 106 - 469 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 508 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -359}
{"prompt": "### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 68 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{", "answer": -179}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 279 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 86 = answer{320} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 455 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 338 = answer{", "answer": -271}
{"prompt": "### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 202 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 135 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 92 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{", "answer": 62}
{"prompt": "### 344 - 409 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{", "answer": 90}
{"prompt": "### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{", "answer": 116}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 197 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 146 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 498 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 167 = answer{", "answer": 82}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 223 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 464 = answer{", "answer": -133}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 374 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 277 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 357 - 370 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 280 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{", "answer": 470}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 463 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 317 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 121 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -54}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 201 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 289 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 292 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 386 = answer{", "answer": 10}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 346 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 192 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 228 = answer{", "answer": 216}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 35 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 202 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 233 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 181 = answer{", "answer": 218}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 239 - 31 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 130 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 275 = answer{", "answer": -240}
{"prompt": "### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 258 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 92 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 452 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 75 = answer{", "answer": 443}
{"prompt": "### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 358 = answer{-251} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 379 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{", "answer": -338}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 51 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 385 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 155 = answer{", "answer": 108}
{"prompt": "### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 394 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 98 = answer{", "answer": 66}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 211 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 450 = answer{", "answer": -337}
{"prompt": "### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 364 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 197 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -203}
{"prompt": "### 170 - 426 = answer{-256} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 391 = answer{", "answer": -117}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 71 = answer{362} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 315 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{", "answer": 160}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 102 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 465 = answer{-326} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 108 = answer{", "answer": -59}
{"prompt": "### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 441 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 71 = answer{362} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 142 = answer{", "answer": 361}
{"prompt": "### 494 - 416 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 208 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 401 = answer{", "answer": -106}
{"prompt": "### 338 - 379 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 374 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 364 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 38 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 113 = answer{", "answer": 324}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 264 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 107 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 224 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 210 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 30 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{", "answer": -362}
{"prompt": "### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 399 = answer{118} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 50 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 146 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 29 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 277 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{", "answer": -141}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 83 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 26 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{", "answer": -319}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 327 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 67 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{", "answer": -109}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 226 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -359}
{"prompt": "### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 19 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{360} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 439 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 277 = answer{", "answer": 157}
{"prompt": "### 316 - 50 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 298 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 69 = answer{", "answer": 94}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 65 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 434 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 454 - 483 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 146 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 98 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 366 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 253 = answer{", "answer": 100}
{"prompt": "### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 2 = answer{", "answer": 455}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 466 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 126 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{", "answer": -21}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 306 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 102 = answer{", "answer": 285}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 27 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 213 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 8 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{", "answer": 323}
{"prompt": "### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 350 = answer{-317} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 237 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 66 - 431 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 235}
{"prompt": "### 406 - 514 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 194 = answer{", "answer": 65}
{"prompt": "### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 237 = answer{-186} ### <eop>\n### 252 - 259 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 438 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 316 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 401 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{", "answer": -284}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 506 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 446 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 183 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 510 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 379 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 323 = answer{", "answer": 71}
{"prompt": "### 400 - 251 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 121 = answer{-3} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 366 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 282 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 419 = answer{", "answer": -346}
{"prompt": "### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 278 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 483 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 269 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 189 = answer{", "answer": 37}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 279 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 292 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{", "answer": 308}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 317 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 130 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 274 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 273 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 177 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 501 = answer{", "answer": -278}
{"prompt": "### 444 - 228 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 293 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 51 = answer{315} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{", "answer": -140}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 448 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{", "answer": 292}
{"prompt": "### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 224 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 326 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 39 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 470 = answer{", "answer": -365}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 428 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 459 = answer{-422} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 418 = answer{", "answer": -275}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 59 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 32 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 320 = answer{", "answer": 8}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 29 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 420 = answer{", "answer": -52}
{"prompt": "### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 117 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 492 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 38 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -313}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 179 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 414 = answer{-381} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 293 = answer{", "answer": -149}
{"prompt": "### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 225 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 110 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 437 = answer{", "answer": -435}
{"prompt": "### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 241 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 180 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{", "answer": 213}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 464 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 46 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 421 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 130 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 497 = answer{", "answer": -220}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 379 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 414 = answer{", "answer": -199}
{"prompt": "### 221 - 126 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 233 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{", "answer": 84}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 188}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 447 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 358 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 208 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 423 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 241 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 335}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 453 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 481 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 59 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{", "answer": 397}
{"prompt": "### 239 - 31 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 174 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 22 - 188 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 249 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 299 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 163 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 22 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 279 = answer{", "answer": -124}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 149 = answer{299} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 130 = answer{", "answer": 259}
{"prompt": "### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 79 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 193 = answer{", "answer": -178}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 503 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 243 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 146 = answer{", "answer": -143}
{"prompt": "### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 385 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 20 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 45}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 0 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 23 - 407 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 428 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 153 = answer{", "answer": 124}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 249 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 388 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 287 = answer{", "answer": 137}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 123 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 284 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 237 = answer{", "answer": -76}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 146 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 368 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 172 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 290 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 200 - 11 = answer{189} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{-396} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 273 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 481 = answer{", "answer": -401}
{"prompt": "### 140 - 97 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 11 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 102 = answer{", "answer": 168}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 261 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 270 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 376 = answer{", "answer": 121}
{"prompt": "### 233 - 179 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 260 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 25 = answer{484} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{", "answer": -277}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 413 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 506 = answer{-505} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{", "answer": 90}
{"prompt": "### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 3 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 21 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 509 = answer{-495} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 164 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 161 = answer{", "answer": 143}
{"prompt": "### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 87 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 144 = answer{-134} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 174 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 183 = answer{", "answer": 239}
{"prompt": "### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 447 = answer{", "answer": -34}
{"prompt": "### 29 - 466 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 350 = answer{", "answer": 110}
{"prompt": "### 483 - 275 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 486 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 368 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 182 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 385 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 416 = answer{", "answer": 78}
{"prompt": "### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 279 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{", "answer": -224}
{"prompt": "### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 178 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 430 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 468 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 289 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{", "answer": -117}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 91 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{452} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{", "answer": 99}
{"prompt": "### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 392 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 168 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 214 = answer{", "answer": -36}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 80 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 260 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 22 - 188 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 204 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 260 = answer{", "answer": 14}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 163 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 262 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 372 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 498 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 420 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 365 = answer{", "answer": -269}
{"prompt": "### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 310 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 196 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 492 = answer{", "answer": -235}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 153 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 169 = answer{-142} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 239 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 500 = answer{-407} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 352 = answer{", "answer": -110}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 146 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 175 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 395 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 50 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 281 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 514 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{", "answer": -455}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 508 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 113 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 99 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 64 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{", "answer": 284}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 177 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 101 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 92 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 292 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{", "answer": 59}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 83 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 94 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 483 = answer{-349} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{", "answer": 459}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 500 = answer{-189} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 277 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 383}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{", "answer": -396}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 367 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -474}
{"prompt": "### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 243 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 260 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 208 = answer{", "answer": 127}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 403 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 0 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 75 = answer{214} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 5 = answer{514} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{", "answer": -219}
{"prompt": "### 429 - 39 = answer{390} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 90 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 212 = answer{", "answer": 221}
{"prompt": "### 502 - 514 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 150 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 50 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 172 = answer{", "answer": 159}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 105 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 472 = answer{17} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 21 = answer{", "answer": 435}
{"prompt": "### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 290 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 308 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 466 = answer{", "answer": -437}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 287 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 79 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 243 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 155 - 279 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 86 = answer{320} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 115 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 488 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{", "answer": -285}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 394 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 171 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 372 - 350 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 457 = answer{", "answer": 19}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 401 - 218 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 47 = answer{386} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 260 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 127 = answer{", "answer": 370}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 113 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 359 - 477 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 180 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 72 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 41 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 80 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{", "answer": -235}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 163 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 440 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 136 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 398 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 394 = answer{", "answer": -298}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 0 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 101 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 402 = answer{", "answer": -170}
{"prompt": "### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 114 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 68 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 235 = answer{", "answer": -172}
{"prompt": "### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 19 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 435 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{", "answer": 86}
{"prompt": "### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 355 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 455 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 42 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 119 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 14 = answer{263} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 231 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 407 = answer{-391} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 390 = answer{", "answer": -293}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 396 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 503 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 383 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 258 = answer{", "answer": -7}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 104 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 117 = answer{", "answer": -101}
{"prompt": "### 376 - 235 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 56 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 116 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 248}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 446 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 102 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 48 = answer{", "answer": 335}
{"prompt": "### 366 - 439 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 20 = answer{353} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 233 = answer{", "answer": -44}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 51 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 31 = answer{377} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 183 = answer{", "answer": -159}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 372 - 350 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 387 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 35 = answer{", "answer": 133}
{"prompt": "### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 461 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 242 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{", "answer": 81}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 2 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{", "answer": 70}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 119 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 59 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 343 = answer{", "answer": 18}
{"prompt": "### 183 - 35 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 256 = answer{-205} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 128}
{"prompt": "### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 64 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{", "answer": -89}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 127 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 224 - 198 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 156}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 252 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 168 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 456 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 14 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 50 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{", "answer": 33}
{"prompt": "### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 251 = answer{-69} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{", "answer": 341}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 98 = answer{182} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 366 = answer{", "answer": -172}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 460 = answer{-392} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{", "answer": 43}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 159 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 500 = answer{-474} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 266 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 446 = answer{", "answer": -66}
{"prompt": "### 314 - 360 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 313 = answer{-150} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 448 = answer{", "answer": -36}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 185 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 361 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 191 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 287 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 438 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 251 = answer{", "answer": 109}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 178 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 91 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 147 = answer{", "answer": 250}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 68 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 394 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{", "answer": 252}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 507 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 469 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 324}
{"prompt": "### 181 - 43 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 274 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{", "answer": 132}
{"prompt": "### 460 - 428 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 91 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 431 = answer{", "answer": -246}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 305 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 194 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{", "answer": -137}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 403 = answer{", "answer": -240}
{"prompt": "### 149 - 488 = answer{-339} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 201 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{-310} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 346 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 298 = answer{", "answer": 52}
{"prompt": "### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 135 = answer{171} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 92 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 27 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 306 = answer{", "answer": -298}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 79 = answer{", "answer": 100}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 509 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 237 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 295 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 77}
{"prompt": "### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 340 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 456 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -169}
{"prompt": "### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 253 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 194 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 340 = answer{", "answer": -97}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 53 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 428 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 177 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 228 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 502 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 287 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 306 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 214 = answer{", "answer": 150}
{"prompt": "### 83 - 26 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 78 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 368 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{", "answer": -97}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 310 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 153 = answer{312} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 51 = answer{", "answer": 331}
{"prompt": "### 77 - 13 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 246 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 233 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 492 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{489} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 199 = answer{", "answer": 190}
{"prompt": "### 429 - 39 = answer{390} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 508 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 486 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{", "answer": 222}
{"prompt": "### 511 - 146 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 69 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 146 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 8 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 292 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 3 = answer{502} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 107 = answer{", "answer": 120}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 267 = answer{12} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{", "answer": -175}
{"prompt": "### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 164 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 140 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 185 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 306 = answer{", "answer": -216}
{"prompt": "### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 305 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 40 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 293 = answer{", "answer": 107}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 195 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 38 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 233 = answer{", "answer": -73}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 159 = answer{177} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 370 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 250 - 42 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 402 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 394 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 276 - 191 = answer{85} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 486 = answer{", "answer": -280}
{"prompt": "### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 196 = answer{", "answer": -54}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 317 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 488 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 41 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 250 = answer{", "answer": 209}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 95 = answer{145} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{", "answer": -248}
{"prompt": "### 435 - 197 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 121 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 47 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 304 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 266 = answer{", "answer": 40}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 460 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 0 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 445 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 158 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 100 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 346 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 204 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 313 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 492 = answer{-296} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 198 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 71 = answer{", "answer": 399}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 338 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -156}
{"prompt": "### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 35 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 295 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 277 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 110 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 373 = answer{", "answer": -144}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 14 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 340 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 497 = answer{-220} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 101 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 157 = answer{", "answer": -125}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 441 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 305 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 278 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{", "answer": -118}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 147 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 294 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 126 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -432}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 179 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 468 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 409 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 179 = answer{", "answer": 169}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 383 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 351 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 486 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 416}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -392}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 307 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 180 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 453 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{", "answer": -172}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 117 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 324 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 143 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 224 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 171 - 337 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 113 = answer{", "answer": 21}
{"prompt": "### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 243 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 447 - 468 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 150 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 361 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 501 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 10 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 428 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{", "answer": -363}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 223 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 214 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -155}
{"prompt": "### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 191 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 4 - 32 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{", "answer": 125}
{"prompt": "### 413 - 107 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 148 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 124 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 150 = answer{", "answer": 277}
{"prompt": "### 373 - 282 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 423 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 354 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 148 = answer{", "answer": 193}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 106 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 340 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 275 = answer{", "answer": -88}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 126 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 70 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 354 = answer{", "answer": -8}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 482 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 140 = answer{", "answer": -135}
{"prompt": "### 425 - 178 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 468 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 196 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 287 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 178 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{", "answer": 275}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 23 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 507 = answer{-418} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 116 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 313 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 269 - 146 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 146 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 185 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 141 - 94 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 439 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 87 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{", "answer": -403}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 364 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 163 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 465 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{", "answer": 328}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 476 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{", "answer": -319}
{"prompt": "### 155 - 238 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 46 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 241 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{", "answer": -46}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{240} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 278 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 126 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 325 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 67 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 413 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 277 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 251 = answer{", "answer": -69}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 485 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 196 = answer{254} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 474 = answer{", "answer": -187}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 241 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 183 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 197 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{", "answer": -54}
{"prompt": "### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 41 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 132 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{", "answer": -289}
{"prompt": "### 403 - 430 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 13 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 420 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{", "answer": -178}
{"prompt": "### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 298 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 486 = answer{", "answer": -192}
{"prompt": "### 89 - 507 = answer{-418} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 241 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 358 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 264 = answer{", "answer": -222}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 102 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 10 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 45 - 6 = answer{", "answer": 39}
{"prompt": "### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 36 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 128 = answer{180} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{", "answer": -292}
{"prompt": "### 141 - 7 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 379 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 276 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{", "answer": -328}
{"prompt": "### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 38 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 55 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{", "answer": -42}
{"prompt": "### 220 - 53 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 31 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 304 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 323 - 263 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 206 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 473 = answer{", "answer": -300}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 240 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 227 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 453 = answer{", "answer": -271}
{"prompt": "### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 197 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 148 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 472 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 66}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 342 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 358 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{", "answer": -77}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 155 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 191 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 242}
{"prompt": "### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 46 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 445 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 55 = answer{391} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 366 = answer{", "answer": -55}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 295 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 169 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 288 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 69 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 68 = answer{", "answer": 196}
{"prompt": "### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 280 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 197 = answer{", "answer": 41}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 113 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 122 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 22 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 364 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 179 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 472 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{", "answer": -287}
{"prompt": "### 387 - 69 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 21 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 37 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{496} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 306 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 335 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 144 = answer{", "answer": 160}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 37 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 109 = answer{", "answer": 89}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 285 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 267 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 99}
{"prompt": "### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 275 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 454 = answer{", "answer": -411}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 233 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 315 = answer{", "answer": -8}
{"prompt": "### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 119 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 430 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 508 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 238}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 80 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 108 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -33}
{"prompt": "### 318 - 236 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 502 = answer{-295} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 456 = answer{", "answer": -78}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 490 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 59 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{", "answer": 410}
{"prompt": "### 76 - 72 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 298 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 91 = answer{", "answer": -43}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 80 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 469 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 139 = answer{260} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 228 = answer{", "answer": 161}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 20 = answer{353} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 321 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 6 = answer{", "answer": 514}
{"prompt": "### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 135 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{", "answer": 222}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 168 - 293 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 174 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 518 = answer{", "answer": -477}
{"prompt": "### 404 - 116 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 370 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 70 = answer{", "answer": 411}
{"prompt": "### 133 - 506 = answer{-373} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 150 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 153 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 71 = answer{362} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 206 = answer{", "answer": 51}
{"prompt": "### 273 - 114 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 17 = answer{", "answer": 476}
{"prompt": "### 204 - 438 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 180 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 292}
{"prompt": "### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 17 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 518 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 98 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{", "answer": 205}
{"prompt": "### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 61 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 18 = answer{", "answer": 321}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 370 = answer{-20} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 374 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 442 = answer{", "answer": 57}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 281 = answer{", "answer": -223}
{"prompt": "### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 333 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 106 - 469 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{", "answer": -212}
{"prompt": "### 181 - 130 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 367 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 187 = answer{", "answer": 100}
{"prompt": "### 38 - 334 = answer{-296} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 275 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 17 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 287}
{"prompt": "### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 115 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 178 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 98 = answer{182} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{", "answer": -223}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 292 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 174 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 40 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 426 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 206 = answer{", "answer": 266}
{"prompt": "### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 119 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 57 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 211 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 6}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 248 = answer{", "answer": -207}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 498 - 385 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 189 = answer{177} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 203 = answer{", "answer": 103}
{"prompt": "### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 25 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 419 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 68 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 213 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 68 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 73 = answer{163} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 421 = answer{", "answer": -117}
{"prompt": "### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 324 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 353}
{"prompt": "### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 60 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 142 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 242 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 93 - 500 = answer{-407} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 160 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 506 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 197 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{", "answer": -169}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 1 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 297 = answer{", "answer": 32}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 298 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 64 - 515 = answer{", "answer": -451}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 7 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 126 = answer{", "answer": 35}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 120 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 351 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 346 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 460 = answer{-392} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 249 = answer{", "answer": -8}
{"prompt": "### 502 - 237 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 170 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 78 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{", "answer": 452}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 460 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 361 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 172 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 197 = answer{", "answer": 109}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 102 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 275 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 132 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 120 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 260 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 135 = answer{171} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{", "answer": 442}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 130 = answer{259} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 430 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{", "answer": -86}
{"prompt": "### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{", "answer": 297}
{"prompt": "### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 142 = answer{361} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 174 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 160 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 232 - 312 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 454 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 421 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 181 = answer{218} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 457}
{"prompt": "### 134 - 113 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 21 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 219 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{", "answer": -198}
{"prompt": "### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 490 = answer{", "answer": -404}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 130 = answer{259} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 85 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 263}
{"prompt": "### 360 - 423 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 389 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 486 = answer{", "answer": -34}
{"prompt": "### 490 - 476 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 216 = answer{-211} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 51 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 383 = answer{", "answer": -303}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 464 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 201 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 440 = answer{", "answer": -191}
{"prompt": "### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 164 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 274 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 60 = answer{", "answer": 9}
{"prompt": "### 379 - 260 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 441 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 385 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 36}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 150 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 441 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 15}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 8 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 178 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{", "answer": 204}
{"prompt": "### 238 - 197 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 281 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 126 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 10 = answer{", "answer": 409}
{"prompt": "### 473 - 200 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 390 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 218 = answer{", "answer": 196}
{"prompt": "### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 235 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 69 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{", "answer": 25}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 412 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 103 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 335 = answer{", "answer": -306}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 107 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 97 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 514 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 377 = answer{", "answer": -72}
{"prompt": "### 11 - 72 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 140 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 42 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{", "answer": 256}
{"prompt": "### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 190 = answer{-107} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 292 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{", "answer": -193}
{"prompt": "### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 147 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{", "answer": 279}
{"prompt": "### 421 - 229 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 288 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 471 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 493 = answer{", "answer": -125}
{"prompt": "### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 206 = answer{293} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 92 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 282 = answer{", "answer": -174}
{"prompt": "### 118 - 292 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 242 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 20 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{", "answer": -203}
{"prompt": "### 254 - 324 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 278}
{"prompt": "### 6 - 30 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 518 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 313 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 323 = answer{151} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 21 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 78 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{", "answer": -194}
{"prompt": "### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 49 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 1 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 169 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 224}
{"prompt": "### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 179 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 169 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 468}
{"prompt": "### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 251 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 113 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{", "answer": -428}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 120 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 164 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 41 = answer{", "answer": 48}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 490 = answer{-320} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 379 = answer{", "answer": -353}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 80 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 269 = answer{", "answer": 155}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 306 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 33 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -281}
{"prompt": "### 401 - 218 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 22 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 125 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 160 = answer{", "answer": 285}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 292 = answer{", "answer": -174}
{"prompt": "### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 196 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 285 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 283 = answer{", "answer": 229}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 55 = answer{391} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 450 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 30 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 94 = answer{", "answer": 47}
{"prompt": "### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 202 = answer{-26} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 246 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 320 = answer{", "answer": -262}
{"prompt": "### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 500 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 275 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 154 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 372 = answer{", "answer": -170}
{"prompt": "### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 414 = answer{-381} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 152 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 507 = answer{-227} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 385 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 149 - 488 = answer{-339} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 485 = answer{", "answer": -87}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 397 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 360 = answer{", "answer": -46}
{"prompt": "### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 425 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 108 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 233 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 324 - 121 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 227 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 195 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 112 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 85 = answer{", "answer": 38}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 160 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 300 = answer{212} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 407 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 143 = answer{", "answer": 302}
{"prompt": "### 25 - 110 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 19 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 147 = answer{", "answer": 197}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 192 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 207 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 417 = answer{", "answer": -213}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 304 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 22 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 328 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{", "answer": -183}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 464 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 28 = answer{468} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 454 - 483 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 260 = answer{", "answer": -260}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 46 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 41 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -260}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 279 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{", "answer": 176}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 476 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 131 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 498 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 481 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 209 = answer{", "answer": 288}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 374 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 108 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 487 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 252 - 259 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 224 = answer{", "answer": 183}
{"prompt": "### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 89 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 453 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 314 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 413 = answer{", "answer": 44}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 278 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 405 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 53 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{370} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 394 = answer{", "answer": 94}
{"prompt": "### 519 - 108 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 90 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{", "answer": 132}
{"prompt": "### 398 - 122 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 53 = answer{167} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 293 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 500 = answer{-407} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 135 = answer{", "answer": 123}
{"prompt": "### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 379 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 90 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 68 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 276 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 142 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 256 = answer{-205} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 476 = answer{", "answer": 3}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 142 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 62 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 28 = answer{468} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -373}
{"prompt": "### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 8 = answer{478} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 236 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 55 = answer{", "answer": -27}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 291 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 200 = answer{", "answer": -122}
{"prompt": "### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 460 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 132 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 107 - 56 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 77 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 490 = answer{-3} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 512 = answer{", "answer": -78}
{"prompt": "### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 372 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 500 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 159 = answer{", "answer": 177}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 115 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 453 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{", "answer": 83}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 472 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 421 = answer{", "answer": -385}
{"prompt": "### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{360} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 98 = answer{", "answer": 25}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 38 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 263 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 31 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 380 - 434 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 183 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 163 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 204 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{", "answer": 202}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 290 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 183 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -181}
{"prompt": "### 82 - 35 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 443 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 283}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 0 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 80 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 441 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{", "answer": 226}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 156 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{240} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{", "answer": -258}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 53 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 22 = answer{", "answer": 333}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 106 = answer{325} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 183 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 206 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 300 = answer{212} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 17 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 353 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 132 = answer{", "answer": 203}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 35 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 14 = answer{429} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 469 = answer{-355} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 14 = answer{263} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -354}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 442 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 61 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 388 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 108 = answer{", "answer": 411}
{"prompt": "### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 300 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{", "answer": -229}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 118 = answer{63} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 502 = answer{", "answer": -295}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 258 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{", "answer": -60}
{"prompt": "### 31 - 414 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 170 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 489 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{", "answer": 202}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{-396} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 170 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{", "answer": -91}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 476 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 116 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 503 = answer{-254} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 325 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 174 = answer{", "answer": 72}
{"prompt": "### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{470} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 56 = answer{", "answer": 220}
{"prompt": "### 262 - 20 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 395 = answer{", "answer": -233}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 166 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 224 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{", "answer": 216}
{"prompt": "### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 252 = answer{", "answer": -116}
{"prompt": "### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 457 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 286}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 368 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 113 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 216 = answer{-211} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 514 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 358 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{", "answer": -8}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 443 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 75 = answer{214} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 120 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 450 = answer{", "answer": 26}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 226 = answer{", "answer": -135}
{"prompt": "### 144 - 293 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 192 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 178 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 51 = answer{", "answer": 315}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 36 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 196 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 343 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 360 - 251 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 94 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 44 = answer{334} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 20 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 338 = answer{", "answer": -290}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 432 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 399 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 117 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 438 = answer{", "answer": -234}
{"prompt": "### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 142 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 313 = answer{-150} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 446 = answer{", "answer": 46}
{"prompt": "### 17 - 393 = answer{-376} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 50 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 298 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 300 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{", "answer": 406}
{"prompt": "### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 456 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 452 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{", "answer": -208}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 113 = answer{45} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 291 = answer{", "answer": -97}
{"prompt": "### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 144 = answer{-134} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 462 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 235 = answer{", "answer": 141}
{"prompt": "### 181 - 314 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 383 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 63 - 259 = answer{-196} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 51 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 365 = answer{-158} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 52 = answer{", "answer": 75}
{"prompt": "### 104 - 113 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 99 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 25 - 110 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 135 = answer{", "answer": 171}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 120 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 158 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{206} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 113 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 83 = answer{", "answer": -81}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 474}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 283 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 175 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{", "answer": 56}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 237 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 50 = answer{", "answer": 266}
{"prompt": "### 227 - 25 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 51 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 153 = answer{", "answer": -135}
{"prompt": "### 187 - 309 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 291 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 411 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{", "answer": -34}
{"prompt": "### 358 - 30 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 172 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 141 = answer{", "answer": 261}
{"prompt": "### 177 - 326 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 189 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 412 = answer{", "answer": 10}
{"prompt": "### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 490 = answer{-320} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 354 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 275 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 25 = answer{193} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 265 = answer{", "answer": 242}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 352 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 385 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 442 - 374 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 132 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 204 = answer{", "answer": 221}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 259 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 409 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{", "answer": 137}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 113 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 38 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 515 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 424 = answer{", "answer": 69}
{"prompt": "### 457 - 423 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 157 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{", "answer": 98}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 14 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 237 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{", "answer": -165}
{"prompt": "### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 56 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -235}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 243 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{", "answer": -18}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{", "answer": 472}
{"prompt": "### 304 - 392 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 503 = answer{-254} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 438 = answer{", "answer": -73}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 320 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 98 = answer{182} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{", "answer": 55}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 281 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 260 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 520 = answer{", "answer": -215}
{"prompt": "### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 460 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 437 = answer{-435} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 204 = answer{", "answer": -171}
{"prompt": "### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 327 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 366 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 131 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{", "answer": -283}
{"prompt": "### 127 - 61 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 320 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 246 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 160 = answer{", "answer": -7}
{"prompt": "### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{360} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 266 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{", "answer": 370}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 450 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 386 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 67 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{", "answer": 74}
{"prompt": "### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 105 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 148 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 121 = answer{", "answer": 18}
{"prompt": "### 401 - 218 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 31 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 115}
{"prompt": "### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 2 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 274 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 1 = answer{", "answer": 175}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 60 = answer{194} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 12 = answer{", "answer": 141}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 19 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 468 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 316 = answer{", "answer": 188}
{"prompt": "### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 377 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 307 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 115 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 317 = answer{", "answer": 115}
{"prompt": "### 470 - 71 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 16 = answer{352} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 414 = answer{", "answer": -383}
{"prompt": "### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{-292} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 165 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 157}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 387 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 148 = answer{", "answer": 311}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 282 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 386 - 82 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 97 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 10 - 355 = answer{-345} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 85 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 293 = answer{", "answer": -36}
{"prompt": "### 86 - 188 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 279 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 80 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 77 = answer{", "answer": -33}
{"prompt": "### 421 - 229 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 396 = answer{-42} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 351 = answer{", "answer": -1}
{"prompt": "### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 375 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 86 = answer{", "answer": 320}
{"prompt": "### 114 - 305 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 101 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 346 = answer{-332} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 468 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 146 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 434 = answer{", "answer": -432}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 377 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 100 - 202 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 116}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 233 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 385 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 67 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{", "answer": -369}
{"prompt": "### 5 - 216 = answer{-211} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 284 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 173 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 9 = answer{102} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 465 = answer{-326} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 496 = answer{", "answer": -9}
{"prompt": "### 175 - 14 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 100 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 258 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{", "answer": -232}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 150 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 300 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{", "answer": 356}
{"prompt": "### 103 - 258 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 115 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 349 = answer{", "answer": 65}
{"prompt": "### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 293 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 394 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 392 = answer{-343} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 316 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 181 = answer{", "answer": 65}
{"prompt": "### 215 - 414 = answer{-199} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 293 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 298 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{", "answer": -160}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 27 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 85 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 293 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 102 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 242}
{"prompt": "### 53 - 318 = answer{-265} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 435 = answer{", "answer": -4}
{"prompt": "### 455 - 471 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 492 = answer{", "answer": -437}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 240 = answer{225} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{-396} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 300 = answer{212} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -157}
{"prompt": "### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 498 - 385 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 485 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 494 - 416 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{452} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 266 = answer{", "answer": 156}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 352 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 89 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 474 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 358 = answer{", "answer": -224}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 498 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 250 = answer{209} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{", "answer": 103}
{"prompt": "### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 82 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 237 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 492 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 213 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 178 = answer{", "answer": 328}
{"prompt": "### 274 - 391 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 349 = answer{", "answer": -280}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 149 = answer{299} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 263 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{", "answer": 22}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 453 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 503 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 402 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 136 = answer{", "answer": 96}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 485 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 138 - 203 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 428 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 124 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 179}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 41 = answer{", "answer": 355}
{"prompt": "### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 148 = answer{", "answer": 195}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{-310} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 25 = answer{484} ### <eop>\n### 4 - 32 = answer{", "answer": -28}
{"prompt": "### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 323 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 498 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 375 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 149 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 2 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 118 = answer{", "answer": 63}
{"prompt": "### 469 - 31 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 394 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 380 = answer{-121} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 92 = answer{", "answer": 392}
{"prompt": "### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 465 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 54 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 95 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 146 = answer{", "answer": -22}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 263 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 440 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 516 = answer{", "answer": -299}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 219 = answer{", "answer": 289}
{"prompt": "### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 236 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 209 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 69 = answer{", "answer": 423}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 290 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 214 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 465 = answer{-326} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 353 = answer{", "answer": 153}
{"prompt": "### 177 - 307 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 223 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 472 = answer{17} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 374 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 469 - 293 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 33 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 281 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 116 = answer{", "answer": 0}
{"prompt": "### 240 - 95 = answer{145} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 153 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 273 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{", "answer": -318}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 281 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 284 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 330}
{"prompt": "### 421 - 164 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 432 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 260 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{", "answer": -208}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 41 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 153 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 60 = answer{", "answer": 194}
{"prompt": "### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{", "answer": -89}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 65 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 259 = answer{-196} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 125 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 272 - 443 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 313 = answer{-150} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 263 = answer{", "answer": -247}
{"prompt": "### 299 - 133 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 335 = answer{", "answer": -288}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 375 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 402}
{"prompt": "### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 64 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 314 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 209 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 95 = answer{145} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{", "answer": -269}
{"prompt": "### 28 - 177 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 119 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 94 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 252 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 261 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 124 = answer{", "answer": -73}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 315 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -232}
{"prompt": "### 12 - 520 = answer{-508} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 492 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 367 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 275 = answer{", "answer": 208}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 132 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 513 = answer{-441} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 116 = answer{", "answer": 231}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 391 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 250 - 42 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{", "answer": -117}
{"prompt": "### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 31 = answer{377} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 182 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 223 - 501 = answer{-278} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 460 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 290 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 8 = answer{478} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 146 = answer{", "answer": -39}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 486 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 438 = answer{", "answer": 49}
{"prompt": "### 126 - 2 = answer{124} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 287 = answer{", "answer": 178}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 181 = answer{218} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 120 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 32 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -380}
{"prompt": "### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 299 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 13 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 163 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 423 = answer{", "answer": -411}
{"prompt": "### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 389 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 279 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -264}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 69 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 146 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{", "answer": -170}
{"prompt": "### 499 - 206 = answer{293} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 375 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{", "answer": 94}
{"prompt": "### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 383 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 179 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 248}
{"prompt": "### 124 - 209 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 31 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{206} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{", "answer": 15}
{"prompt": "### 13 - 260 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 486 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 259 = answer{", "answer": -196}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 206 = answer{", "answer": 293}
{"prompt": "### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 169 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 183 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 87 = answer{", "answer": 318}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 369 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 304 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 67 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{", "answer": -139}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 400 = answer{", "answer": -351}
{"prompt": "### 32 - 8 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 209 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 498 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{", "answer": 147}
{"prompt": "### 24 - 183 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 430 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 365 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{", "answer": 200}
{"prompt": "### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 352 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{", "answer": -290}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 106 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 115 - 409 = answer{-294} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 300 = answer{", "answer": -173}
{"prompt": "### 187 - 275 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 506 = answer{-505} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 237 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 25 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 156 = answer{", "answer": -94}
{"prompt": "### 49 - 392 = answer{-343} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 41 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{", "answer": 26}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 246 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 514 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 44 = answer{334} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 197 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{", "answer": -397}
{"prompt": "### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 16 = answer{352} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 35 = answer{", "answer": 379}
{"prompt": "### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 3 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 417 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 334 = answer{", "answer": 98}
{"prompt": "### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 308 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 9 = answer{102} ### <eop>\n### 103 - 258 = answer{", "answer": -155}
{"prompt": "### 233 - 179 = answer{54} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 385 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 374 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 495 = answer{-396} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{370} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 435 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 33 = answer{", "answer": 37}
{"prompt": "### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 169 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 148 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{", "answer": 172}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 20 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 463 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 317 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 515}
{"prompt": "### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 104 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 352 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 91 = answer{-32} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 83 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 70 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 323 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 273 = answer{", "answer": 232}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 198 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 193 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 210 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 207 = answer{", "answer": -76}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 109 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 45 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{406} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 365 = answer{", "answer": -158}
{"prompt": "### 82 - 118 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 163 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 152 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 206 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 130 = answer{", "answer": 72}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 266 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 89 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 500 = answer{-189} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 483 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 344 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 497 = answer{-220} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 62 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 20 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 287 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{", "answer": 61}
{"prompt": "### 245 - 419 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{406} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 23 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 287 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 50 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -464}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 287 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 195 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{", "answer": 35}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 109 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 155 = answer{", "answer": 144}
{"prompt": "### 367 - 241 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 130 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 313 = answer{-150} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 405 = answer{", "answer": 112}
{"prompt": "### 18 - 153 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 404 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 475 = answer{", "answer": -445}
{"prompt": "### 472 - 206 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 466 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 147 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 102 - 405 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 100 - 202 = answer{", "answer": -102}
{"prompt": "### 486 - 175 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 325 = answer{", "answer": -245}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 71 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 126 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 520 = answer{", "answer": -508}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 80 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 298 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 111 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{", "answer": -384}
{"prompt": "### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 167 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 455 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{", "answer": 338}
{"prompt": "### 103 - 258 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 439 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 30 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 87}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 337 - 368 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 36 = answer{", "answer": 159}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 476 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 113 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 393 = answer{-376} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 278 = answer{", "answer": -77}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 134 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 116 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 490 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 374 = answer{", "answer": -116}
{"prompt": "### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 297 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 424 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{", "answer": 160}
{"prompt": "### 420 - 49 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 380 = answer{-121} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 416 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 357 = answer{", "answer": -98}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -91}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 118 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 21 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 29 = answer{", "answer": 398}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 51 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 79 = answer{", "answer": 178}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 107 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 234 = answer{", "answer": 119}
{"prompt": "### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 113 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 119 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 83 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 325}
{"prompt": "### 445 - 308 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 360 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 71 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 386 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 31 = answer{438} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 272 = answer{", "answer": 174}
{"prompt": "### 513 - 159 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{452} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 485 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 493 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 206 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 148}
{"prompt": "### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 446 = answer{-124} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 340 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{", "answer": -82}
{"prompt": "### 452 - 195 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 264 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 484 = answer{", "answer": 35}
{"prompt": "### 361 - 119 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 354 = answer{-219} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 242 = answer{", "answer": 52}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 248 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 122 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 224 = answer{", "answer": 140}
{"prompt": "### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 462 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 37 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 410 = answer{", "answer": -114}
{"prompt": "### 360 - 287 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 242 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 188 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 300 = answer{212} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{", "answer": -55}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 0}
{"prompt": "### 3 - 146 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 107 = answer{241} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 106 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{", "answer": 419}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 435 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 80 = answer{384} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 362 = answer{", "answer": -240}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 219 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 317 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{432} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 132}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 124 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -188}
{"prompt": "### 52 - 214 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 346 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 56 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 123 = answer{", "answer": 397}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 476 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 69 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 455 = answer{", "answer": -5}
{"prompt": "### 289 - 75 = answer{214} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 174 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 453 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 401 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 290 = answer{", "answer": 84}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 193 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 283 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{", "answer": 38}
{"prompt": "### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 267 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 94 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 305 = answer{", "answer": -130}
{"prompt": "### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 156 = answer{133} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 172 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 364 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 301 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 62 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 36 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{", "answer": -59}
{"prompt": "### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 464 = answer{", "answer": -463}
{"prompt": "### 127 - 61 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 50 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 455 - 471 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 295 = answer{", "answer": 75}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 442 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 228 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 375 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 396 = answer{", "answer": -108}
{"prompt": "### 410 - 64 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 443 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 216 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 236 = answer{", "answer": 167}
{"prompt": "### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 7 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 366 - 445 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 259 = answer{-196} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 9 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 437 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 455 = answer{", "answer": -179}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 221 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 423 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 511 = answer{", "answer": -102}
{"prompt": "### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 95 = answer{", "answer": -95}
{"prompt": "### 315 - 198 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 484 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 443 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 149 = answer{", "answer": 93}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 120 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 153 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 152 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 427 = answer{", "answer": -291}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 5 = answer{514} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 362 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 170 = answer{", "answer": 305}
{"prompt": "### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 38 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 490 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{", "answer": -21}
{"prompt": "### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 109 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 424 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 4 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 228 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 455 - 471 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 114 - 327 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 147 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 249 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{", "answer": 81}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 94 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 19 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 337 = answer{", "answer": -184}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 199 = answer{268} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 426 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 107 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{", "answer": 169}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 90 = answer{406} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 339 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 219 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 259 = answer{", "answer": 74}
{"prompt": "### 85 - 9 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 347 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 260 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 264 = answer{", "answer": 42}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 440 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 43 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 7 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 290 = answer{", "answer": 210}
{"prompt": "### 391 - 432 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 130 = answer{106} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 177 = answer{", "answer": -149}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 175 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -120}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 20 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 243 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 285 = answer{", "answer": 44}
{"prompt": "### 87 - 89 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 196 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 359 - 477 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 291 = answer{", "answer": 175}
{"prompt": "### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 173 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 59 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 180 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{", "answer": 47}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 128 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 119 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 484 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 66 = answer{", "answer": 13}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 459 = answer{-422} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 124 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 374 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 413 = answer{", "answer": -266}
{"prompt": "### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 281 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{", "answer": 0}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 226 = answer{-30} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 140 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 267 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 240 = answer{", "answer": 259}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 413 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 239 = answer{", "answer": 154}
{"prompt": "### 35 - 50 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 520 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 30 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 508 = answer{", "answer": -262}
{"prompt": "### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 350 = answer{-317} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 284 = answer{", "answer": -246}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 292 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 78 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 66 - 431 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 472}
{"prompt": "### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 275 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 358 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 40 = answer{-25} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 465 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{", "answer": 51}
{"prompt": "### 441 - 413 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 229 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 107 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 114 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 443 = answer{", "answer": -61}
{"prompt": "### 148 - 26 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 120 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 104 - 113 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 292 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 375 = answer{", "answer": -291}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 127 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 428 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 339 = answer{", "answer": -31}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 173 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 182 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 483 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 53 - 318 = answer{-265} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 160 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 263 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 229 = answer{", "answer": 38}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 115 - 409 = answer{-294} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 372 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 240 = answer{", "answer": -238}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 249 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 244 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 83 = answer{311} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{", "answer": 309}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 425 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 405 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 260 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 413 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 445 - 160 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 264 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 91 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 374 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 286 = answer{", "answer": -176}
{"prompt": "### 237 - 260 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 119 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 221}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 101 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 221 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 132 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 214 = answer{", "answer": -179}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 206 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 506 = answer{-373} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 421 - 5 = answer{416} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 401 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 183 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 474 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 338 = answer{", "answer": -145}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 122 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 453 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 249 - 440 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 279 = answer{-276} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 413 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 178 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{", "answer": -44}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 185 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{", "answer": -177}
{"prompt": "### 49 - 407 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 306 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{", "answer": 2}
{"prompt": "### 65 - 226 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 298 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 471 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 373 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 225 = answer{", "answer": 205}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 105 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 38 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 508 = answer{", "answer": -203}
{"prompt": "### 132 - 0 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 471 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 52 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -337}
{"prompt": "### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 27 = answer{91} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 90 = answer{", "answer": 373}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 132 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 209 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 210 = answer{-50} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 432}
{"prompt": "### 139 - 401 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 265 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 247 = answer{", "answer": -115}
{"prompt": "### 452 - 486 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 213 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 439 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 76 = answer{", "answer": 355}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 194 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 105 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 410 - 64 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 358 = answer{", "answer": 42}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 27 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 420 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 53 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 310 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 237 = answer{", "answer": -32}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 43 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 158 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 222 - 445 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 7 = answer{", "answer": 228}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 344 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 468 = answer{", "answer": -176}
{"prompt": "### 333 - 193 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 228 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 31 = answer{300} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 351 = answer{", "answer": -88}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 481 = answer{-387} ### <eop>\n### 454 - 483 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 13 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 116 = answer{", "answer": 288}
{"prompt": "### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 83 = answer{-81} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 417 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 328 = answer{", "answer": -34}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 343 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 5 = answer{514} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 259 = answer{", "answer": -71}
{"prompt": "### 98 - 433 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{", "answer": 111}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 376 = answer{121} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 257 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 464 = answer{-463} ### <eop>\n### 462 - 255 = answer{", "answer": 207}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 281 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 446 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 7 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 435 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 64 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{", "answer": 98}
{"prompt": "### 484 - 488 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 269 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 354 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 337 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -225}
{"prompt": "### 497 - 503 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 308 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 328 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 281 - 469 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 4 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 454 = answer{-411} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{", "answer": 140}
{"prompt": "### 261 - 238 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 169 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 520 = answer{", "answer": -302}
{"prompt": "### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 220 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 284 = answer{-228} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 282 = answer{", "answer": -2}
{"prompt": "### 176 - 428 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 206 = answer{293} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 112 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -297}
{"prompt": "### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 251 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 27 = answer{", "answer": 327}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 61 = answer{363} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 394 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 357 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 123 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 295 = answer{", "answer": -172}
{"prompt": "### 402 - 130 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 152 = answer{156} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 410 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 490 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{", "answer": -250}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 199 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 146 = answer{365} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 201 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 59 = answer{", "answer": 331}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 242 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 280 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 44 - 77 = answer{-33} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 315 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{", "answer": 75}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 126 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 142 = answer{", "answer": 94}
{"prompt": "### 412 - 406 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -252}
{"prompt": "### 273 - 313 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 147 = answer{", "answer": 59}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 513 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 298 = answer{", "answer": 154}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 70 = answer{411} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 280 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 129 = answer{", "answer": 269}
{"prompt": "### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 417 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 472 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{", "answer": -45}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 395 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 170 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 281 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 329}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 50 = answer{431} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 314 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 460 = answer{", "answer": -46}
{"prompt": "### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 17 - 223 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 200 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 349 = answer{", "answer": -330}
{"prompt": "### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 257 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 395 = answer{-233} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -358}
{"prompt": "### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 441 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 175 = answer{", "answer": 311}
{"prompt": "### 116 - 277 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 456 = answer{-77} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 326 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{", "answer": -362}
{"prompt": "### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 272 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 469 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 59 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 452 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 30 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 281 = answer{224} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{", "answer": 247}
{"prompt": "### 148 - 483 = answer{-335} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 146 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 130 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 46 = answer{292} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 225 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 38 = answer{", "answer": 394}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 100 - 202 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 155 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 175 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 215 - 312 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 405 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 197 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 372 - 350 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{", "answer": 271}
{"prompt": "### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 161 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 164 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 33 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{", "answer": 152}
{"prompt": "### 105 - 143 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 59 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 110 = answer{-62} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 363}
{"prompt": "### 9 - 298 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 421 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{", "answer": 176}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 394 = answer{", "answer": -250}
{"prompt": "### 0 - 31 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 324 = answer{", "answer": 11}
{"prompt": "### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 22 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 104 = answer{256} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 192 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 270 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 37 - 437 = answer{-400} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 295 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -119}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 440 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 417 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 156 = answer{", "answer": 133}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 224 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{", "answer": 82}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 225 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 10 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 242 = answer{", "answer": -66}
{"prompt": "### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 288 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 218 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 471 = answer{", "answer": -177}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 346 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{", "answer": -253}
{"prompt": "### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 80 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 205 = answer{228} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 377 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{", "answer": -420}
{"prompt": "### 23 - 89 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 422 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 272 = answer{", "answer": 28}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 243 = answer{-91} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 453 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 465 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{", "answer": -215}
{"prompt": "### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 214 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 404 = answer{", "answer": -194}
{"prompt": "### 146 - 466 = answer{-320} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 209 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 40 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 77 = answer{", "answer": 426}
{"prompt": "### 452 - 67 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 320 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 32 = answer{323} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{", "answer": 109}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 336 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 293 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 481 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 282 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 170 = answer{", "answer": -98}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 285 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 191 = answer{302} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{", "answer": -52}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 97 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 341 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 460 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 500 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 49 = answer{", "answer": 371}
{"prompt": "### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 249 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 389 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 36 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 69 = answer{", "answer": 111}
{"prompt": "### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 92 = answer{392} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{", "answer": 326}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 335 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 75 = answer{214} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 500 = answer{-474} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{", "answer": 172}
{"prompt": "### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 136 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 471 = answer{-455} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{", "answer": -389}
{"prompt": "### 294 - 328 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 441 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{", "answer": -318}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 422 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 322 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 252 = answer{", "answer": 239}
{"prompt": "### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 128 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 341 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 164 = answer{", "answer": 19}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 309 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 193 = answer{", "answer": 142}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 409 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 25 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 233 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 407 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 79 - 98 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 228 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{", "answer": -113}
{"prompt": "### 447 - 493 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 72 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 373 = answer{-144} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 341 = answer{", "answer": -301}
{"prompt": "### 202 - 372 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 368 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 282 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 55 = answer{", "answer": 391}
{"prompt": "### 160 - 447 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 251 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 159 = answer{177} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 414 = answer{-381} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 179 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 65 - 226 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 243 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 241 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{", "answer": -201}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 498 = answer{", "answer": -363}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 38 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 44 = answer{334} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 376}
{"prompt": "### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 179 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 304 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 62 = answer{", "answer": 318}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 338 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 57 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{", "answer": -84}
{"prompt": "### 347 - 116 = answer{231} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 285 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 56 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 439 = answer{", "answer": -437}
{"prompt": "### 47 - 242 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 195 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 206 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 183 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 27 = answer{", "answer": 476}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 88 = answer{4} ### <eop>\n### 262 - 340 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 267 = answer{12} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 231 = answer{", "answer": -71}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 152 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -344}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{", "answer": 371}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 99 = answer{246} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 214 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{", "answer": -99}
{"prompt": "### 405 - 289 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 106 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 485 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 512 = answer{", "answer": -101}
{"prompt": "### 50 - 172 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 320 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 495 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 101 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 327 = answer{", "answer": -213}
{"prompt": "### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 260 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 75 = answer{443} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 233 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 212 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 196 = answer{-45} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{", "answer": 131}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 428 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 293 = answer{", "answer": 176}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 417 - 177 = answer{", "answer": 240}
{"prompt": "### 134 - 358 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 396 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 87 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 435 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 198 = answer{", "answer": 117}
{"prompt": "### 472 - 206 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 366 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 261 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 258}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 110 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 355 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 146 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 178 = answer{", "answer": 25}
{"prompt": "### 330 - 231 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 225 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 407 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 123 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 61 = answer{13} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{", "answer": -238}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 160 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 351 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 375 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{", "answer": -153}
{"prompt": "### 234 - 482 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 300 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 106 = answer{", "answer": 395}
{"prompt": "### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 258 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 32 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{", "answer": 239}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 16 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 243 = answer{", "answer": -151}
{"prompt": "### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 490 = answer{-3} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 225 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 102 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -108}
{"prompt": "### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 402 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 29 = answer{398} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 174 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 446}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 120 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 372 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 395 = answer{-354} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 438 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 202 = answer{", "answer": -17}
{"prompt": "### 393 - 357 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 478 - 92 = answer{", "answer": 386}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 330 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 430 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{", "answer": -224}
{"prompt": "### 322 - 349 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 309 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 43 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 257 = answer{", "answer": -187}
{"prompt": "### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 338 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 51 = answer{315} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 267 = answer{-212} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 4 = answer{", "answer": 298}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 0 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 515 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 88 = answer{", "answer": 4}
{"prompt": "### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 494 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 440 = answer{", "answer": -13}
{"prompt": "### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 69 - 349 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 408 = answer{-378} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{", "answer": -316}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 352 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 90 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 159 - 406 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 187 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 53 = answer{", "answer": 289}
{"prompt": "### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 217 = answer{-141} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 213 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 370 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{", "answer": -18}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 181 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 187 - 309 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{436} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 152 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{", "answer": 205}
{"prompt": "### 181 - 314 = answer{-133} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 4 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 430 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 463 - 90 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{", "answer": 29}
{"prompt": "### 133 - 7 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 360 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 120 = answer{329} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 89 = answer{", "answer": 287}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 382 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{470} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 500 = answer{-474} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 11}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 519 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 263 = answer{-247} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{", "answer": -226}
{"prompt": "### 29 - 161 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 69 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 50 = answer{", "answer": 170}
{"prompt": "### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 287 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 252 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 112 - 477 = answer{", "answer": -365}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 197 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 221 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 500 = answer{-407} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{", "answer": 120}
{"prompt": "### 368 - 16 = answer{352} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 197 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 240 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 404 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 240 = answer{", "answer": 225}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 59 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 33 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 379 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 142 - 195 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{", "answer": 67}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 205 = answer{228} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 253 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 5 = answer{515} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 176 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{", "answer": -188}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 272 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 358 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 247 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 509 = answer{", "answer": -495}
{"prompt": "### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 172 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 320 = answer{", "answer": 186}
{"prompt": "### 352 - 456 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 256 = answer{-205} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 496 = answer{-210} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 89 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 44 = answer{334} ### <eop>\n### 11 - 72 = answer{", "answer": -61}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 135 = answer{171} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 510 = answer{-484} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 488 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 124 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{", "answer": -51}
{"prompt": "### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 415 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 58 = answer{", "answer": 436}
{"prompt": "### 357 - 335 = answer{22} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 453 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 408 = answer{", "answer": -378}
{"prompt": "### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 513 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 472 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 21 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 84}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 275 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 236 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 497 = answer{-220} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{", "answer": 351}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{489} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 169 - 233 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 311 = answer{31} ### <eop>\n### 25 - 110 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 434 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 230 = answer{", "answer": -55}
{"prompt": "### 445 - 315 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 273 - 114 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 430 = answer{-307} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 147 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 122 = answer{", "answer": -113}
{"prompt": "### 460 - 350 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 27 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 361 = answer{", "answer": -136}
{"prompt": "### 519 - 267 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 461 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{", "answer": 139}
{"prompt": "### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 98 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 410 - 64 = answer{", "answer": 346}
{"prompt": "### 156 - 26 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 122 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 480 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 183 = answer{", "answer": -37}
{"prompt": "### 170 - 426 = answer{-256} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 3 = answer{502} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 26 = answer{", "answer": 399}
{"prompt": "### 310 - 253 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 370 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 416 = answer{", "answer": -402}
{"prompt": "### 198 - 109 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 447 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 39 = answer{283} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 426 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 490 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 98 = answer{", "answer": 182}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 64 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 466 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{", "answer": 148}
{"prompt": "### 253 - 100 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 437 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 116 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 420 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 268 = answer{", "answer": -234}
{"prompt": "### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 98 - 274 = answer{", "answer": -176}
{"prompt": "### 193 - 474 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 329 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 501 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 35 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 31 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{", "answer": -239}
{"prompt": "### 457 - 423 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 21 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 125}
{"prompt": "### 51 - 57 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 250 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 87 = answer{318} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 15 = answer{454} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{", "answer": 385}
{"prompt": "### 350 - 370 = answer{-20} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 190 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 458 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 40 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 256 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 67 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 190 = answer{", "answer": 310}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 376 = answer{121} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{", "answer": 127}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 328 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 195 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 460 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 489}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 420 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 443 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 180 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{", "answer": 101}
{"prompt": "### 287 - 175 = answer{112} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 365 = answer{", "answer": 70}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 164 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 397 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 30 = answer{", "answer": 48}
{"prompt": "### 162 - 109 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{470} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 167 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 368 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 173 = answer{", "answer": 62}
{"prompt": "### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 8 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 5 = answer{287} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 310 = answer{", "answer": -215}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 53 - 318 = answer{-265} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 407 = answer{", "answer": -162}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 420 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 224 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 482 - 436 = answer{", "answer": 46}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 291 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 459 = answer{-422} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 456 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{", "answer": -323}
{"prompt": "### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 290 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 358 = answer{", "answer": 161}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 159 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 233 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 310 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 471 - 477 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 518 = answer{-314} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 23 = answer{", "answer": 179}
{"prompt": "### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 358 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 358 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 258 = answer{", "answer": -255}
{"prompt": "### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 328 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 61 = answer{", "answer": -11}
{"prompt": "### 89 - 41 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 259 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 219}
{"prompt": "### 231 - 65 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 165 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 514 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 360 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 333 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 413 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{", "answer": 387}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 185 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 410 = answer{", "answer": 110}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 149 = answer{299} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 19 = answer{489} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 252 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 352 = answer{", "answer": 107}
{"prompt": "### 75 - 422 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 327 = answer{-213} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 383 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 27 = answer{", "answer": 91}
{"prompt": "### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 352 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 146 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{", "answer": -128}
{"prompt": "### 229 - 252 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 446 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 61 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 486 = answer{", "answer": -126}
{"prompt": "### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 67 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{", "answer": 265}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 25 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 214 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 472 = answer{", "answer": -81}
{"prompt": "### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 119 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 156 = answer{133} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 358 = answer{-251} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 428 = answer{", "answer": -366}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 249 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{", "answer": -37}
{"prompt": "### 418 - 439 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 466 = answer{-320} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 360 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 228 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 169 = answer{", "answer": 74}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 79 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 59 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 178 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 442 = answer{", "answer": -231}
{"prompt": "### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 169 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 146 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 502 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 104 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 465 = answer{", "answer": -326}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 9 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 246 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 83 = answer{", "answer": 7}
{"prompt": "### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 41 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 80 = answer{195} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 219 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 144 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{", "answer": 319}
{"prompt": "### 136 - 10 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 91 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 70 = answer{397} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 328 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 91 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{", "answer": 217}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 319 = answer{-316} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 470 = answer{", "answer": -297}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 284 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 425 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 266 = answer{", "answer": 56}
{"prompt": "### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 207 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 309 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -82}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 30 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 208 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 46 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -20}
{"prompt": "### 79 - 98 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 109 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 274 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 394 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 291}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 281 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 36 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 456 = answer{", "answer": -104}
{"prompt": "### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 327 - 250 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 354 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{", "answer": -80}
{"prompt": "### 517 - 399 = answer{118} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 409 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 66 - 431 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 112 - 409 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 64 = answer{", "answer": 15}
{"prompt": "### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 146 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{", "answer": 226}
{"prompt": "### 192 - 67 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 152 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{", "answer": 81}
{"prompt": "### 393 - 459 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 399 = answer{118} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 394 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 437 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 459 = answer{", "answer": -422}
{"prompt": "### 187 - 309 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 410 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 238 = answer{", "answer": -14}
{"prompt": "### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{", "answer": 119}
{"prompt": "### 489 - 472 = answer{17} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 387 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 240 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 161 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 43 = answer{", "answer": 379}
{"prompt": "### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 203 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 384 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -288}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 117 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 56 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 111 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 125 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 372 - 350 = answer{", "answer": 22}
{"prompt": "### 329 - 297 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 507 = answer{5} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 50 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 325 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 193 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 323 = answer{151} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 209 = answer{288} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 215 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 288 = answer{", "answer": -169}
{"prompt": "### 311 - 366 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 370 = answer{-20} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{-324} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 302 - 468 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 173 - 470 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 66 - 431 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 480 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 498 = answer{", "answer": -109}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{181} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 500 = answer{-189} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 293 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 198 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{", "answer": 134}
{"prompt": "### 412 - 265 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 100 - 202 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 219 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 290 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 219 = answer{", "answer": -44}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 317 = answer{80} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 241 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 324 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 285 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 113 = answer{", "answer": 114}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 389 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 137 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 153 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 409 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 317 = answer{", "answer": -18}
{"prompt": "### 125 - 119 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 515 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 514 = answer{", "answer": -12}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 273 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 508 = answer{", "answer": -179}
{"prompt": "### 504 - 123 = answer{381} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 385 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 26 = answer{", "answer": 481}
{"prompt": "### 508 - 219 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 421 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{", "answer": 139}
{"prompt": "### 356 - 218 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 247 - 17 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 135 - 332 = answer{", "answer": -197}
{"prompt": "### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 418 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 384 = answer{-358} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 76 = answer{355} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{", "answer": -92}
{"prompt": "### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 220 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 283 = answer{", "answer": -63}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 164 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 459 = answer{", "answer": 33}
{"prompt": "### 409 - 449 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 137 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 488 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 214 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 241 = answer{", "answer": -198}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 192 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 410 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 87 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{", "answer": 297}
{"prompt": "### 507 - 26 = answer{481} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 48 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 123 = answer{97} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 469 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 390 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 66 - 431 = answer{", "answer": -365}
{"prompt": "### 273 - 313 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 324 = answer{-70} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 294 - 328 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 3 = answer{", "answer": 188}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 72 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 81 = answer{272} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 360 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 144 = answer{-100} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{", "answer": 110}
{"prompt": "### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 325 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 359 - 477 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 249 = answer{", "answer": -38}
{"prompt": "### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 140 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 10 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 317 = answer{80} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 318 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 196 - 226 = answer{-30} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 91 = answer{", "answer": -32}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 196 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 292 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 202 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 306 = answer{", "answer": -159}
{"prompt": "### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 385 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 339 = answer{-52} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 119 = answer{242} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 164 = answer{", "answer": 122}
{"prompt": "### 486 - 44 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 21 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 386 = answer{-285} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -15}
{"prompt": "### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 253 - 100 = answer{153} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{", "answer": -207}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 163 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{", "answer": -268}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 336 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 215 - 414 = answer{-199} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 444 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 464 = answer{-218} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 98 = answer{", "answer": -19}
{"prompt": "### 326 - 485 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 59 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 426 = answer{", "answer": -256}
{"prompt": "### 68 - 178 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 164 = answer{122} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 520 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 310 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 306 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 19 = answer{", "answer": 227}
{"prompt": "### 165 - 221 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 256 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 425 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 74 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 193 = answer{", "answer": 245}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 455 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 64 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 418 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 447 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 290}
{"prompt": "### 167 - 39 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 322 = answer{55} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 12 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 432 = answer{", "answer": 34}
{"prompt": "### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 169 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 235 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 114 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 68 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 354 = answer{", "answer": 76}
{"prompt": "### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 106 - 469 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 485 = answer{-87} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{", "answer": 92}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 432 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 35 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 123 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 414 = answer{-381} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{", "answer": 57}
{"prompt": "### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 512 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 395 = answer{", "answer": -354}
{"prompt": "### 346 - 40 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 299 - 155 = answer{144} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 149 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -339}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 46 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 293 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 75 = answer{443} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 375 = answer{", "answer": -28}
{"prompt": "### 438 - 193 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 80 - 325 = answer{-245} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 25 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 241 - 259 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 83 = answer{191} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 153 = answer{124} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 163 = answer{", "answer": -64}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 464 = answer{-463} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 300 = answer{", "answer": 212}
{"prompt": "### 66 - 431 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 420 = answer{", "answer": 56}
{"prompt": "### 214 - 99 = answer{115} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 22 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 72 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 380 = answer{", "answer": -80}
{"prompt": "### 2 - 240 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 442 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 487 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 266 = answer{156} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 138 = answer{", "answer": 3}
{"prompt": "### 287 - 187 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 16 = answer{309} ### <eop>\n### 112 - 477 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{", "answer": -5}
{"prompt": "### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 413 = answer{44} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 48 = answer{", "answer": 219}
{"prompt": "### 309 - 405 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 85 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 436 = answer{-37} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 423 = answer{", "answer": -63}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 361 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 378 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 260 = answer{", "answer": -23}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 299 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{", "answer": 65}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 472 = answer{17} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 143 = answer{302} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 29 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 306 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 114 = answer{", "answer": 64}
{"prompt": "### 86 - 10 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 225 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 430 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 123 = answer{", "answer": 1}
{"prompt": "### 176 - 428 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 287 - 474 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 503 = answer{-254} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{", "answer": 190}
{"prompt": "### 72 - 170 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 108 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 297 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -185}
{"prompt": "### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 409 = answer{-313} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 51 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 453 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 171 - 337 = answer{", "answer": -166}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 380 = answer{-121} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 52 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 298 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 447 = answer{", "answer": -287}
{"prompt": "### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 110 = answer{", "answer": -62}
{"prompt": "### 175 - 219 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 110 = answer{101} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 416 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 344 = answer{", "answer": -165}
{"prompt": "### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 506 - 344 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 140 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 201 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 226 = answer{", "answer": -30}
{"prompt": "### 62 - 159 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 87 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 116 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 169 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 183 = answer{", "answer": 147}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 418 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 288 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 177 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 161 = answer{", "answer": 275}
{"prompt": "### 129 - 386 = answer{-257} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 358 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 361 = answer{", "answer": -138}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 128 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 38 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 500 - 290 = answer{210} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 336 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 418 = answer{-240} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 222 - 445 = answer{", "answer": -223}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 301 = answer{-53} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 410 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 197 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 224 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -254}
{"prompt": "### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 299 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 310 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 195 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 197 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 370 = answer{", "answer": -281}
{"prompt": "### 466 - 304 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 258 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 65 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 462 = answer{", "answer": -309}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 299 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 311 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 228 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 432 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 155}
{"prompt": "### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 235 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 453 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 463 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 79 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{-469} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 21 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{", "answer": -92}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 453 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 184 = answer{277} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{360} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{", "answer": -180}
{"prompt": "### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 77 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 99 = answer{", "answer": 246}
{"prompt": "### 159 - 281 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 225 = answer{173} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 26 = answer{399} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 258 = answer{96} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 35 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 309 = answer{", "answer": 141}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 91 = answer{-43} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 488 = answer{-380} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{", "answer": -321}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 251 = answer{-69} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{-292} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 113 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 25 = answer{484} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 178 = answer{", "answer": 247}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 93 - 307 = answer{-214} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 113 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 102 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 77 = answer{", "answer": 181}
{"prompt": "### 102 - 405 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 442 = answer{-439} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 428 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 210 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 347 = answer{", "answer": 5}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 274 = answer{-255} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 24 = answer{442} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 26 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 216 = answer{-211} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 216 = answer{", "answer": -44}
{"prompt": "### 420 - 49 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 29 = answer{211} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 9 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 484 - 488 = answer{", "answer": -4}
{"prompt": "### 308 - 128 = answer{180} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 11 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 453 - 474 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 503 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 217 - 520 = answer{", "answer": -303}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 458 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 173 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 370 = answer{-346} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 412 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 443 = answer{", "answer": 54}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 131 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 244 - 69 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 411 = answer{-237} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 328 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 367 = answer{", "answer": 108}
{"prompt": "### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 50 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 500 = answer{-494} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 435 = answer{", "answer": -106}
{"prompt": "### 245 - 419 = answer{-174} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 19 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 155 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 297 = answer{", "answer": -149}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 158 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 341 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 128 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 428 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 185 = answer{", "answer": 74}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 174 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 260 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 508 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 267 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 266 = answer{", "answer": 134}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 165 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 482 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 2 = answer{", "answer": 346}
{"prompt": "### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 17 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 155 - 238 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 207 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 460 = answer{-392} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 186 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 198 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 379 = answer{", "answer": 8}
{"prompt": "### 275 - 134 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 102 - 405 = answer{-303} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 503 = answer{-254} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 304 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 27 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 457 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 59 - 442 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 410 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 183 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{", "answer": -68}
{"prompt": "### 241 - 259 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 396 - 386 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 434 = answer{-310} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 288 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 374 = answer{", "answer": -231}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 491 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 382 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 91 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 502 = answer{", "answer": -151}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 21 - 198 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 123 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 441 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 293 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{", "answer": 70}
{"prompt": "### 276 - 56 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 175 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 276 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 502 = answer{", "answer": -469}
{"prompt": "### 476 - 21 = answer{455} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 177 - 107 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 31 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{", "answer": -194}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 137 = answer{203} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 241 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 28 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 89 - 507 = answer{", "answer": -418}
{"prompt": "### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 119 = answer{278} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 152 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 122 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 468 = answer{-284} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 430 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 483 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 490 = answer{", "answer": -3}
{"prompt": "### 106 - 469 = answer{-363} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 407 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 102 = answer{285} ### <eop>\n### 401 - 218 = answer{", "answer": 183}
{"prompt": "### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 501 = answer{-278} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 99 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 490 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 296 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 24 = answer{", "answer": 481}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 488 = answer{-337} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 287 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 344 = answer{-175} ### <eop>\n### 402 - 141 = answer{261} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 36 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 209 = answer{", "answer": 265}
{"prompt": "### 1 - 429 = answer{-428} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 12 = answer{419} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 25 = answer{243} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 449 = answer{-289} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 462 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 231 - 65 = answer{", "answer": 166}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 281 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{206} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 279 = answer{", "answer": -86}
{"prompt": "### 49 - 255 = answer{-206} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 219 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 260 = answer{", "answer": 119}
{"prompt": "### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 319 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 46 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 435 = answer{", "answer": -11}
{"prompt": "### 360 - 251 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{-304} ### <eop>\n### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{", "answer": -110}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 19 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 433}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 188 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 324 = answer{", "answer": -75}
{"prompt": "### 475 - 367 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 26 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 325 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 243 - 170 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 316 = answer{-270} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 189 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 346 = answer{", "answer": 58}
{"prompt": "### 8 - 243 = answer{-235} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 391 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 320 = answer{-262} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 256 = answer{-205} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 352 = answer{", "answer": -201}
{"prompt": "### 506 - 320 = answer{186} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 17 = answer{476} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{-292} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 21 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -63}
{"prompt": "### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 221 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 346 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 166 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 133 = answer{", "answer": 313}
{"prompt": "### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 485 = answer{-277} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 475 = answer{", "answer": -200}
{"prompt": "### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{407} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 233 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 55 - 492 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 15 = answer{", "answer": 379}
{"prompt": "### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 305 = answer{-130} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 383 - 509 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 28 = answer{", "answer": 229}
{"prompt": "### 335 - 208 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 507 = answer{-253} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 456 = answer{-104} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 291 = answer{140} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 196 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 243 = answer{-187} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 13 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 396 = answer{-126} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 262 = answer{", "answer": 23}
{"prompt": "### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 245 = answer{-47} ### <eop>\n### 250 - 42 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 374 = answer{-116} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 140 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 240 - 57 = answer{183} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 4 - 32 = answer{-28} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 404 = answer{", "answer": 108}
{"prompt": "### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 469 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 43 - 241 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 442 = answer{", "answer": -439}
{"prompt": "### 62 - 142 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 167 = answer{152} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 209 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 196 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{", "answer": 421}
{"prompt": "### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 97 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 20 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 390 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 500 - 314 = answer{", "answer": 186}
{"prompt": "### 129 - 277 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 137 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 292 = answer{-292} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 175 = answer{", "answer": 105}
{"prompt": "### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 344 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 11 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 264 = answer{42} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{", "answer": -111}
{"prompt": "### 26 - 370 = answer{-344} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 399 = answer{118} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 113 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 449 = answer{", "answer": -40}
{"prompt": "### 217 - 516 = answer{-299} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 37 = answer{394} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 313 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 211 - 249 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 382 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 191 = answer{", "answer": 302}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 437 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 496 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 428 = answer{-366} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 49 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{", "answer": 100}
{"prompt": "### 165 - 391 = answer{-226} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 160 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 179 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 52 - 365 = answer{", "answer": -313}
{"prompt": "### 382 - 443 = answer{-61} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 168 = answer{92} ### <eop>\n### 212 - 294 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 425 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 46 = answer{", "answer": 261}
{"prompt": "### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 379 = answer{-195} ### <eop>\n### 364 - 159 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 361 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 430 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{", "answer": 116}
{"prompt": "### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 397 = answer{", "answer": -16}
{"prompt": "### 394 - 280 = answer{114} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 170 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 213 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 298 = answer{154} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 201 = answer{", "answer": -5}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 197 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 78 = answer{298} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 19 = answer{227} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 343 = answer{", "answer": -225}
{"prompt": "### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 495 - 176 = answer{319} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 272 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 394 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 239 - 31 = answer{", "answer": 208}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{198} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 72 = answer{327} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 108 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 216 - 348 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 98 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 276 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 147 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 448 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 299 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 210 = answer{", "answer": -50}
{"prompt": "### 94 - 481 = answer{-387} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 368 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 430 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 135 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 276 - 191 = answer{", "answer": 85}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 149 = answer{93} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 293 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 511 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 486 = answer{-483} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 429}
{"prompt": "### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 86 = answer{320} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 80 = answer{356} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{", "answer": 83}
{"prompt": "### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 95 = answer{385} ### <eop>\n### 29 - 232 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 203 = answer{172} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 2 = answer{", "answer": 124}
{"prompt": "### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 0 = answer{46} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 457 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 30 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 415 = answer{", "answer": -10}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 165 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 453 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 25 = answer{", "answer": 243}
{"prompt": "### 381 - 115 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 391 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 130 = answer{72} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 437 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 193 = answer{", "answer": 140}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 497 = answer{-220} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 324 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 264 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 509 = answer{", "answer": -115}
{"prompt": "### 111 - 11 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 205 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 20 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 441 = answer{-193} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 456 = answer{", "answer": -394}
{"prompt": "### 191 - 395 = answer{-204} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 432 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 354 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 432 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 127 = answer{", "answer": 291}
{"prompt": "### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 373 - 291 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 499 = answer{-315} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 178 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 443 = answer{", "answer": -225}
{"prompt": "### 358 - 156 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 213 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 377 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{", "answer": -74}
{"prompt": "### 434 - 512 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 110 = answer{204} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 147 = answer{250} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{345} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 179 = answer{", "answer": 245}
{"prompt": "### 475 - 367 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 386 - 82 = answer{304} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 438 = answer{", "answer": -282}
{"prompt": "### 416 - 299 = answer{117} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 125 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 126 = answer{95} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 158 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 115 = answer{", "answer": 266}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 77 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 424 = answer{-111} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 316 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 276 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 365 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{", "answer": -364}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 277 = answer{-261} ### <eop>\n### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 354 = answer{30} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 72 = answer{", "answer": 398}
{"prompt": "### 183 - 269 = answer{-86} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 125 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 502 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 235 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 305 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 336 = answer{", "answer": -132}
{"prompt": "### 454 - 483 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 30 = answer{48} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 223 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 357 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 334 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 321 = answer{", "answer": 127}
{"prompt": "### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 286 - 160 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 201 = answer{-162} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 251 = answer{", "answer": 149}
{"prompt": "### 388 - 260 = answer{128} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 520 = answer{-508} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 306 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{", "answer": 185}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 160 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 91 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 113 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 344 = answer{", "answer": -190}
{"prompt": "### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 136 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 322 = answer{", "answer": -113}
{"prompt": "### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 80 = answer{384} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 344 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 98 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{", "answer": -182}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 343 = answer{27} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{255} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 76 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 0 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 422 = answer{", "answer": 14}
{"prompt": "### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 471 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 460 - 390 = answer{", "answer": 70}
{"prompt": "### 158 - 121 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{", "answer": -79}
{"prompt": "### 240 - 234 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 177 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 416 = answer{-402} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 283 - 219 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 494 = answer{", "answer": -24}
{"prompt": "### 370 - 295 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 209 = answer{-190} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 154 = answer{253} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 412 = answer{", "answer": -50}
{"prompt": "### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 456 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 180 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 36 - 181 = answer{", "answer": -145}
{"prompt": "### 242 - 411 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 111 = answer{326} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 181 = answer{218} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 13 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 266 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 70 = answer{", "answer": 201}
{"prompt": "### 442 - 55 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 112 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 201 = answer{217} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{-90} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 459 = answer{", "answer": -66}
{"prompt": "### 498 - 385 = answer{113} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 409 = answer{-331} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 275 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 363 - 510 = answer{-147} ### <eop>\n### 510 - 415 = answer{", "answer": 95}
{"prompt": "### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 379 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 326 - 485 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 301 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 274 = answer{", "answer": -177}
{"prompt": "### 176 - 242 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 491 = answer{-338} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 245 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 452 - 195 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 279 = answer{", "answer": -276}
{"prompt": "### 452 - 208 = answer{244} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 115 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -294}
{"prompt": "### 133 - 461 = answer{-328} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 471 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 272 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 341 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 16 = answer{", "answer": 276}
{"prompt": "### 306 - 222 = answer{84} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 41 = answer{379} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 99 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 140 - 97 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{", "answer": -267}
{"prompt": "### 492 - 456 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 440 = answer{-180} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 428 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 188 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 183 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 152 = answer{", "answer": 329}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 43 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 480 = answer{-397} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 219 = answer{289} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 464 = answer{-342} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{", "answer": -443}
{"prompt": "### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 289 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 483 - 275 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{", "answer": -426}
{"prompt": "### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 428 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 227 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 53 = answer{", "answer": -14}
{"prompt": "### 362 - 196 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 456 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 392 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 247 = answer{-115} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 377 = answer{", "answer": -330}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 413 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 90 = answer{", "answer": 60}
{"prompt": "### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 72 - 170 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 305 = answer{-191} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{", "answer": 86}
{"prompt": "### 343 - 128 = answer{215} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 374 = answer{-231} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 42 = answer{", "answer": 109}
{"prompt": "### 167 - 439 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 484 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 250 - 42 = answer{208} ### <eop>\n### 130 - 489 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 130 = answer{", "answer": 51}
{"prompt": "### 19 - 349 = answer{-330} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 473 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 123 - 430 = answer{-307} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 360 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 91 - 174 = answer{", "answer": -83}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 258 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 350 - 370 = answer{-20} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 112 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 250 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 450 - 368 = answer{", "answer": 82}
{"prompt": "### 208 - 375 = answer{-167} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 5 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 240 - 95 = answer{145} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 207 = answer{219} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 192 = answer{", "answer": 178}
{"prompt": "### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 175 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{", "answer": -197}
{"prompt": "### 163 - 238 = answer{-75} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 435 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 380 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 40 - 285 = answer{-245} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 153 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 201 = answer{", "answer": 217}
{"prompt": "### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 312 - 469 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 510 = answer{-432} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -359}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 380 - 154 = answer{226} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 181 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 378 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 57 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 345 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 179 - 115 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 65 = answer{155} ### <eop>\n### 388 - 411 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 334 = answer{", "answer": -296}
{"prompt": "### 436 - 360 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 471 - 361 = answer{", "answer": 110}
{"prompt": "### 502 - 514 = answer{-12} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 114 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 461 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 237 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 316 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 11 = answer{", "answer": 189}
{"prompt": "### 131 - 207 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{201} ### <eop>\n### 378 - 456 = answer{-78} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 183 = answer{222} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 511 = answer{", "answer": -288}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 159 = answer{177} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 442 - 277 = answer{165} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 13 = answer{387} ### <eop>\n### 437 - 422 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{", "answer": 257}
{"prompt": "### 318 - 258 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 91 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 509 = answer{", "answer": -151}
{"prompt": "### 422 - 261 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 262 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 61 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 226 = answer{-19} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 292 = answer{200} ### <eop>\n### 140 - 97 = answer{", "answer": 43}
{"prompt": "### 382 - 51 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 47 = answer{470} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 183 = answer{239} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 460 = answer{-429} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 343 = answer{64} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 277 = answer{", "answer": -261}
{"prompt": "### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 254 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 94 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 85 - 382 = answer{-297} ### <eop>\n### 431 - 5 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 429 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 390}
{"prompt": "### 97 - 256 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 152 = answer{156} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 428 = answer{-156} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 118 = answer{", "answer": 21}
{"prompt": "### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 13 = answer{395} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 161 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 40 = answer{", "answer": 306}
{"prompt": "### 107 - 56 = answer{51} ### <eop>\n### 251 - 82 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 152 - 463 = answer{-311} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{", "answer": 192}
{"prompt": "### 277 - 278 = answer{-1} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 439 = answer{-437} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 272 = answer{174} ### <eop>\n### 511 - 146 = answer{", "answer": 365}
{"prompt": "### 168 - 293 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 323 - 300 = answer{23} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 299 = answer{", "answer": 181}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 281 - 469 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 251 = answer{58} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 405 = answer{-319} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 31 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 398 = answer{", "answer": -70}
{"prompt": "### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 466 - 291 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 270 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 67 = answer{", "answer": 273}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 396 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 461 = answer{-194} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 288 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 110 - 469 = answer{-359} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 382 = answer{", "answer": -65}
{"prompt": "### 301 - 439 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 99 - 56 = answer{43} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 500 = answer{-474} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 248 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 284 = answer{", "answer": -228}
{"prompt": "### 383 - 48 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 221 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 380 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 489 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 498 = answer{-404} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -74}
{"prompt": "### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 329 = answer{-160} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 502 = answer{-295} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 394 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 277 = answer{", "answer": -76}
{"prompt": "### 465 - 153 = answer{312} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{284} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 329 - 508 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 484 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{", "answer": -148}
{"prompt": "### 215 - 414 = answer{-199} ### <eop>\n### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 241 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 372 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 226 - 189 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 37 = answer{", "answer": 301}
{"prompt": "### 368 - 16 = answer{352} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 457 = answer{-389} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 21 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 14 = answer{", "answer": 158}
{"prompt": "### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 387 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 275 - 412 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 489 = answer{-192} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 439 = answer{", "answer": -21}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 149 = answer{299} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 90 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 103 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 249 - 300 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 507 = answer{", "answer": 5}
{"prompt": "### 144 - 293 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 135 = answer{271} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 144 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 174 - 411 = answer{-237} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{157} ### <eop>\n### 95 - 325 = answer{", "answer": -230}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 275 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 77 - 121 = answer{-44} ### <eop>\n### 183 - 73 = answer{110} ### <eop>\n### 400 - 314 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 253 = answer{-230} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 260 = answer{", "answer": -247}
{"prompt": "### 237 - 260 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 178 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 224 - 385 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 227 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 227 = answer{290} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 54 = answer{", "answer": 201}
{"prompt": "### 16 - 105 = answer{-89} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 385 = answer{-54} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 230 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 145 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 125 - 39 = answer{", "answer": 86}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 370 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 97 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 490 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 0 = answer{", "answer": 395}
{"prompt": "### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 150 = answer{248} ### <eop>\n### 415 - 429 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 392 - 303 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 137 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 23 = answer{", "answer": 411}
{"prompt": "### 456 - 30 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 184 - 416 = answer{-232} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 0 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 56 - 19 = answer{37} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{", "answer": 24}
{"prompt": "### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 253 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 407 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 306 = answer{", "answer": -40}
{"prompt": "### 448 - 512 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 300 - 380 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 445 = answer{-178} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 414 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 15 = answer{366} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -318}
{"prompt": "### 91 - 226 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 7 = answer{228} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 395 = answer{-140} ### <eop>\n### 164 - 98 = answer{66} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 142 = answer{-80} ### <eop>\n### 333 - 95 = answer{", "answer": 238}
{"prompt": "### 294 - 471 = answer{-177} ### <eop>\n### 92 - 243 = answer{-151} ### <eop>\n### 369 - 39 = answer{330} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 295 = answer{-145} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 352 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{", "answer": 20}
{"prompt": "### 207 - 76 = answer{131} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 148 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 69 = answer{423} ### <eop>\n### 514 - 55 = answer{459} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 360 - 287 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 305 - 108 = answer{197} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 239 = answer{-76} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 503 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 354 = answer{-321} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 127 = answer{", "answer": -14}
{"prompt": "### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 428 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 513 = answer{-280} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 506 = answer{-464} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 82 - 118 = answer{", "answer": -36}
{"prompt": "### 396 - 386 = answer{10} ### <eop>\n### 454 - 483 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 33 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 38 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 231 = answer{", "answer": 255}
{"prompt": "### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 215 = answer{-72} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 352 = answer{107} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 291 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 17 = answer{", "answer": 280}
{"prompt": "### 406 - 444 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 42 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 404 = answer{-282} ### <eop>\n### 264 - 115 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 162}
{"prompt": "### 71 - 100 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 91 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 105 - 489 = answer{-384} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 105 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 416 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 272 - 494 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 5 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{-356} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 288 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 469 = answer{", "answer": -4}
{"prompt": "### 147 - 80 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 332 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 32 - 6 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 202 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 113 - 57 = answer{56} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 452 = answer{", "answer": -109}
{"prompt": "### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 163 = answer{213} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 241 - 411 = answer{-170} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 432 = answer{", "answer": -324}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 224 = answer{68} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 122 - 261 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 363 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 357 = answer{", "answer": 36}
{"prompt": "### 313 - 409 = answer{-96} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 415 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 210 - 31 = answer{179} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 501 = answer{-420} ### <eop>\n### 328 - 319 = answer{", "answer": 9}
{"prompt": "### 219 - 114 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 231 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 385 = answer{-288} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 6 = answer{341} ### <eop>\n### 15 - 40 = answer{", "answer": -25}
{"prompt": "### 339 - 277 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 291 - 399 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 511 = answer{-102} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 231 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{", "answer": 206}
{"prompt": "### 69 - 60 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 60 = answer{148} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 457 = answer{-443} ### <eop>\n### 365 - 175 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 280 = answer{", "answer": 114}
{"prompt": "### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 399 - 237 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 294 = answer{-93} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 392 = answer{-383} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 490 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 216 - 348 = answer{-132} ### <eop>\n### 515 - 137 = answer{378} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 391 - 308 = answer{83} ### <eop>\n### 199 - 204 = answer{-5} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 2 = answer{", "answer": 286}
{"prompt": "### 227 - 25 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 441 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 368 = answer{-94} ### <eop>\n### 165 - 338 = answer{-173} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 134 = answer{", "answer": 136}
{"prompt": "### 288 - 396 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 144 - 293 = answer{-149} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 496 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 84 - 272 = answer{-188} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 215 = answer{", "answer": -72}
{"prompt": "### 42 - 264 = answer{-222} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 360 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 427 - 291 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 164 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 379 - 260 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 313 - 34 = answer{", "answer": 279}
{"prompt": "### 310 - 253 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 339 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 195 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 444 - 306 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 381 - 400 = answer{", "answer": -19}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 379 = answer{-41} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 244 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 473 - 21 = answer{452} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 64 = answer{15} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 385 = answer{", "answer": -77}
{"prompt": "### 212 - 366 = answer{-154} ### <eop>\n### 218 - 520 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 338 = answer{100} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 270 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 28 = answer{402} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 476 = answer{", "answer": 14}
{"prompt": "### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 357 - 370 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 516 - 29 = answer{487} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 177 = answer{175} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 28 = answer{229} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 472 = answer{", "answer": -356}
{"prompt": "### 263 - 1 = answer{262} ### <eop>\n### 173 - 491 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 158 = answer{-49} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 99 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 464 = answer{", "answer": -218}
{"prompt": "### 443 - 275 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 400 = answer{-250} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 490 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 226 = answer{-30} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 68 = answer{", "answer": 190}
{"prompt": "### 271 - 112 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 496 = answer{-9} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 321 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 233 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 224 = answer{", "answer": 56}
{"prompt": "### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 434 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 190 - 183 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 402 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 409 - 488 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 315 - 242 = answer{", "answer": 73}
{"prompt": "### 295 - 126 = answer{169} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{-101} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 311 = answer{-74} ### <eop>\n### 274 - 260 = answer{14} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 414 = answer{-287} ### <eop>\n### 19 - 209 = answer{", "answer": -190}
{"prompt": "### 408 - 70 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 100 = answer{351} ### <eop>\n### 58 - 266 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 375 - 65 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 325 - 119 = answer{206} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 384 = answer{", "answer": -358}
{"prompt": "### 355 - 22 = answer{333} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 427 = answer{-291} ### <eop>\n### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 460 = answer{-392} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 495 = answer{", "answer": -401}
{"prompt": "### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 477 - 292 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 374 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 3 = answer{405} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 173 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -157}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 482 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 259 - 185 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 230 - 253 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 384 - 30 = answer{", "answer": 354}
{"prompt": "### 425 - 178 = answer{247} ### <eop>\n### 44 - 123 = answer{-79} ### <eop>\n### 494 - 416 = answer{78} ### <eop>\n### 307 - 225 = answer{82} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 155 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 0 - 111 = answer{", "answer": -111}
{"prompt": "### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 470 - 494 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 281 = answer{71} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 214 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 315 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 306 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 368 - 339 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 231 = answer{-197} ### <eop>\n### 270 - 267 = answer{", "answer": 3}
{"prompt": "### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 159 = answer{354} ### <eop>\n### 196 - 80 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 181 = answer{164} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 350 = answer{", "answer": -317}
{"prompt": "### 300 - 65 = answer{235} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 51 = answer{315} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 203 - 15 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 313 = answer{-239} ### <eop>\n### 447 - 493 = answer{", "answer": -46}
{"prompt": "### 179 - 17 = answer{162} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 53 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 394 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 143 = answer{338} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 249 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 111 - 11 = answer{", "answer": 100}
{"prompt": "### 505 - 3 = answer{502} ### <eop>\n### 408 - 133 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 153 - 12 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 318 - 236 = answer{", "answer": 82}
{"prompt": "### 110 - 286 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 3 - 146 = answer{-143} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 349 = answer{", "answer": -27}
{"prompt": "### 336 - 484 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 16 - 185 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 22 - 188 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 76 = answer{", "answer": 99}
{"prompt": "### 494 - 400 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 116 - 323 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 395 - 379 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 47 - 137 = answer{", "answer": -90}
{"prompt": "### 446 - 133 = answer{313} ### <eop>\n### 200 - 385 = answer{-185} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 415 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 198 - 263 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 496 - 368 = answer{", "answer": 128}
{"prompt": "### 39 - 53 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 322 - 281 = answer{41} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 343 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 63 - 279 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 281 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 170 - 490 = answer{", "answer": -320}
{"prompt": "### 297 - 17 = answer{280} ### <eop>\n### 292 - 281 = answer{11} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 520 - 5 = answer{515} ### <eop>\n### 435 - 197 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 481 = answer{", "answer": -387}
{"prompt": "### 473 - 221 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 160 = answer{1} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 161 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 472 = answer{-31} ### <eop>\n### 108 - 21 = answer{", "answer": 87}
{"prompt": "### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 467 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 160 - 121 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 503 = answer{-283} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 165 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 311 - 500 = answer{", "answer": -189}
{"prompt": "### 391 - 375 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 197 - 248 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 469 - 293 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 426 = answer{-403} ### <eop>\n### 295 - 417 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 252 - 259 = answer{", "answer": -7}
{"prompt": "### 153 - 337 = answer{-184} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 76 - 314 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 415 = answer{-10} ### <eop>\n### 41 - 518 = answer{-477} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 9 = answer{", "answer": 39}
{"prompt": "### 427 - 249 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 459 = answer{33} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 201 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 9 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 488 - 31 = answer{457} ### <eop>\n### 233 - 513 = answer{", "answer": -280}
{"prompt": "### 173 - 473 = answer{-300} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 135 = answer{-56} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 338 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 106 = answer{368} ### <eop>\n### 223 - 501 = answer{-278} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 386 = answer{", "answer": 113}
{"prompt": "### 273 - 428 = answer{-155} ### <eop>\n### 238 - 357 = answer{-119} ### <eop>\n### 242 - 411 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 215 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 202 - 265 = answer{-63} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 196 = answer{", "answer": 155}
{"prompt": "### 78 - 350 = answer{-272} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 252 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 23 - 296 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 449 = answer{-16} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 441 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 37 - 5 = answer{", "answer": 32}
{"prompt": "### 373 - 20 = answer{353} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 267 = answer{252} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 251 = answer{-82} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 284 - 381 = answer{-97} ### <eop>\n### 232 - 312 = answer{", "answer": -80}
{"prompt": "### 235 - 173 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 355 = answer{52} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 242 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 149 - 488 = answer{-339} ### <eop>\n### 284 - 381 = answer{", "answer": -97}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 179 = answer{270} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 361 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 12 - 250 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 433 - 303 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 508 = answer{-84} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 214 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 380 - 446 = answer{-66} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 43 = answer{360} ### <eop>\n### 491 - 200 = answer{291} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 281 = answer{20} ### <eop>\n### 411 - 28 = answer{383} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 145 = answer{", "answer": 41}
{"prompt": "### 412 - 380 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 138 - 203 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 172 - 46 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 120 - 144 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{", "answer": -223}
{"prompt": "### 315 - 242 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 286 = answer{35} ### <eop>\n### 62 - 456 = answer{-394} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 447 = answer{40} ### <eop>\n### 448 - 321 = answer{127} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 160 = answer{", "answer": 188}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 19 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 301 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 277 - 153 = answer{124} ### <eop>\n### 256 - 408 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{86} ### <eop>\n### 297 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 284}
{"prompt": "### 374 - 275 = answer{99} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 90 - 306 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 39 - 53 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 418 - 402 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 105 - 470 = answer{-365} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 264 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 450 = answer{26} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 273 = answer{232} ### <eop>\n### 75 - 422 = answer{", "answer": -347}
{"prompt": "### 341 - 173 = answer{168} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 397 - 281 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 310 - 430 = answer{-120} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 481 = answer{-128} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{", "answer": -137}
{"prompt": "### 307 - 315 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 87 - 89 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 46 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 39 = answer{418} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 135 = answer{132} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 437 = answer{", "answer": -86}
{"prompt": "### 359 - 477 = answer{-118} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 20 = answer{335} ### <eop>\n### 389 - 199 = answer{190} ### <eop>\n### 255 - 270 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 305 - 520 = answer{-215} ### <eop>\n### 266 - 128 = answer{", "answer": 138}
{"prompt": "### 397 - 404 = answer{-7} ### <eop>\n### 248 - 240 = answer{8} ### <eop>\n### 367 - 286 = answer{81} ### <eop>\n### 358 - 506 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 347 - 313 = answer{34} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 104 = answer{", "answer": 257}
{"prompt": "### 137 - 345 = answer{-208} ### <eop>\n### 26 - 379 = answer{-353} ### <eop>\n### 78 - 200 = answer{-122} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 327 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 423 - 333 = answer{90} ### <eop>\n### 508 - 12 = answer{", "answer": 496}
{"prompt": "### 124 - 233 = answer{-109} ### <eop>\n### 343 - 207 = answer{136} ### <eop>\n### 156 - 26 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 5 = answer{129} ### <eop>\n### 225 - 454 = answer{-229} ### <eop>\n### 308 - 128 = answer{", "answer": 180}
{"prompt": "### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 443 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 466 = answer{-309} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 476 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 316 - 50 = answer{266} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 123 = answer{", "answer": 97}
{"prompt": "### 80 - 481 = answer{-401} ### <eop>\n### 169 - 471 = answer{-302} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 299 = answer{-136} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 361 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{", "answer": -48}
{"prompt": "### 14 - 509 = answer{-495} ### <eop>\n### 314 - 466 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 130 = answer{106} ### <eop>\n### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 186 - 99 = answer{87} ### <eop>\n### 25 - 110 = answer{", "answer": -85}
{"prompt": "### 127 - 52 = answer{75} ### <eop>\n### 162 - 333 = answer{-171} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 193 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 117 - 146 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 359 - 477 = answer{", "answer": -118}
{"prompt": "### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 247 = answer{185} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 351 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 28 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 351 - 282 = answer{69} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 315 = answer{", "answer": 130}
{"prompt": "### 276 - 455 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 60 = answer{194} ### <eop>\n### 222 - 445 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 519 - 1 = answer{518} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 450 = answer{", "answer": 9}
{"prompt": "### 509 - 244 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 393 - 357 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 166 - 435 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 405 - 415 = answer{-10} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 164 = answer{-67} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 50 = answer{", "answer": 431}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 352 = answer{-201} ### <eop>\n### 118 - 343 = answer{-225} ### <eop>\n### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 20 = answer{482} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 441 = answer{-106} ### <eop>\n### 446 - 360 = answer{", "answer": 86}
{"prompt": "### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 352 - 420 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 436 - 161 = answer{275} ### <eop>\n### 6 - 4 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 60 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{", "answer": 331}
{"prompt": "### 390 - 436 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 257 - 79 = answer{178} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 215 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 60 = answer{421} ### <eop>\n### 178 - 214 = answer{-36} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 69 = answer{", "answer": 318}
{"prompt": "### 292 - 150 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 263 - 351 = answer{-88} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 54 = answer{192} ### <eop>\n### 175 - 14 = answer{161} ### <eop>\n### 129 - 386 = answer{", "answer": -257}
{"prompt": "### 20 - 14 = answer{6} ### <eop>\n### 219 - 3 = answer{216} ### <eop>\n### 331 - 254 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 193 - 261 = answer{-68} ### <eop>\n### 441 - 413 = answer{28} ### <eop>\n### 480 - 307 = answer{", "answer": 173}
{"prompt": "### 241 - 259 = answer{-18} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 35 - 10 = answer{25} ### <eop>\n### 42 - 369 = answer{-327} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 142 = answer{297} ### <eop>\n### 505 - 3 = answer{", "answer": 502}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 296 - 410 = answer{-114} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 237 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 324 - 461 = answer{-137} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{", "answer": 36}
{"prompt": "### 6 - 30 = answer{-24} ### <eop>\n### 151 - 444 = answer{-293} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 503 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 119 = answer{-85} ### <eop>\n### 303 - 367 = answer{-64} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 265 = answer{", "answer": 157}
{"prompt": "### 364 - 159 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 31 - 354 = answer{-323} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 39 = answer{221} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 242 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 377 - 309 = answer{", "answer": 68}
{"prompt": "### 37 - 5 = answer{32} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 155 = answer{49} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 69 = answer{94} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 267 = answer{12} ### <eop>\n### 304 - 421 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 13 - 238 = answer{", "answer": -225}
{"prompt": "### 317 - 168 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 344 = answer{70} ### <eop>\n### 282 - 280 = answer{2} ### <eop>\n### 161 - 19 = answer{142} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 53 - 318 = answer{", "answer": -265}
{"prompt": "### 56 - 430 = answer{-374} ### <eop>\n### 57 - 347 = answer{-290} ### <eop>\n### 227 - 267 = answer{-40} ### <eop>\n### 30 - 153 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 390 = answer{-183} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{", "answer": -146}
{"prompt": "### 323 - 263 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 146 - 466 = answer{-320} ### <eop>\n### 141 - 138 = answer{3} ### <eop>\n### 205 - 366 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 301 - 185 = answer{116} ### <eop>\n### 509 - 25 = answer{", "answer": 484}
{"prompt": "### 90 - 83 = answer{7} ### <eop>\n### 204 - 78 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 456 - 21 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 513 - 415 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 48 - 319 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 245 - 72 = answer{", "answer": 173}
{"prompt": "### 392 - 335 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 384 = answer{-364} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 440 - 210 = answer{230} ### <eop>\n### 370 - 46 = answer{324} ### <eop>\n### 9 - 298 = answer{", "answer": -289}
{"prompt": "### 48 - 9 = answer{39} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 518 - 108 = answer{410} ### <eop>\n### 425 - 389 = answer{36} ### <eop>\n### 185 - 431 = answer{-246} ### <eop>\n### 512 - 383 = answer{", "answer": 129}
{"prompt": "### 461 - 115 = answer{346} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 183 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 2 - 240 = answer{-238} ### <eop>\n### 464 - 426 = answer{38} ### <eop>\n### 342 - 452 = answer{-110} ### <eop>\n### 70 - 171 = answer{", "answer": -101}
{"prompt": "### 333 - 95 = answer{238} ### <eop>\n### 134 - 113 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 434 - 61 = answer{373} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 430 = answer{-95} ### <eop>\n### 490 - 18 = answer{472} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 389 = answer{", "answer": -109}
{"prompt": "### 449 - 470 = answer{-21} ### <eop>\n### 96 - 294 = answer{-198} ### <eop>\n### 109 - 47 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 147 = answer{59} ### <eop>\n### 445 - 169 = answer{276} ### <eop>\n### 133 - 7 = answer{", "answer": 126}
{"prompt": "### 512 - 404 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 280 - 175 = answer{105} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 3 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 398 - 129 = answer{269} ### <eop>\n### 126 - 3 = answer{123} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 101 = answer{", "answer": 402}
{"prompt": "### 445 - 315 = answer{130} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 355 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 229 - 489 = answer{-260} ### <eop>\n### 321 - 101 = answer{220} ### <eop>\n### 320 - 55 = answer{265} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 420 = answer{", "answer": -313}
{"prompt": "### 491 - 506 = answer{-15} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 362 = answer{139} ### <eop>\n### 288 - 396 = answer{-108} ### <eop>\n### 195 - 97 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 220 - 503 = answer{", "answer": -283}
{"prompt": "### 385 - 512 = answer{-127} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 118 = answer{63} ### <eop>\n### 481 - 173 = answer{308} ### <eop>\n### 361 - 343 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 236 - 110 = answer{126} ### <eop>\n### 348 - 150 = answer{", "answer": 198}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 509 = answer{-169} ### <eop>\n### 403 - 430 = answer{-27} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 355 = answer{-301} ### <eop>\n### 346 - 40 = answer{306} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 201 - 207 = answer{", "answer": -6}
{"prompt": "### 461 - 490 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 278 - 443 = answer{-165} ### <eop>\n### 493 - 469 = answer{24} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 439 = answer{29} ### <eop>\n### 150 - 90 = answer{60} ### <eop>\n### 420 - 13 = answer{", "answer": 407}
{"prompt": "### 276 - 314 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 316 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 369 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 14 - 361 = answer{-347} ### <eop>\n### 507 - 331 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 279 - 267 = answer{", "answer": 12}
{"prompt": "### 92 - 175 = answer{-83} ### <eop>\n### 51 - 124 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 153 = answer{312} ### <eop>\n### 517 - 43 = answer{474} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 100 = answer{", "answer": -29}
{"prompt": "### 368 - 493 = answer{-125} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 339 - 18 = answer{321} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 413 = answer{-148} ### <eop>\n### 145 - 463 = answer{-318} ### <eop>\n### 502 - 237 = answer{", "answer": 265}
{"prompt": "### 414 - 218 = answer{196} ### <eop>\n### 332 - 46 = answer{286} ### <eop>\n### 33 - 350 = answer{-317} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{16} ### <eop>\n### 24 - 183 = answer{-159} ### <eop>\n### 180 - 217 = answer{", "answer": -37}
{"prompt": "### 91 - 230 = answer{-139} ### <eop>\n### 366 - 439 = answer{-73} ### <eop>\n### 476 - 105 = answer{371} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 221 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 207 - 488 = answer{-281} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 310 = answer{", "answer": -39}
{"prompt": "### 257 - 295 = answer{-38} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 3 = answer{188} ### <eop>\n### 235 - 158 = answer{77} ### <eop>\n### 194 - 346 = answer{-152} ### <eop>\n### 271 - 209 = answer{62} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 256 = answer{", "answer": -159}
{"prompt": "### 178 - 31 = answer{147} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 227 = answer{160} ### <eop>\n### 61 - 67 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 260 - 311 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 439 - 238 = answer{", "answer": 201}
{"prompt": "### 354 - 14 = answer{340} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 1 = answer{19} ### <eop>\n### 107 - 146 = answer{-39} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 460 = answer{-46} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 67 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 20 - 131 = answer{", "answer": -111}
{"prompt": "### 90 - 306 = answer{-216} ### <eop>\n### 390 - 231 = answer{159} ### <eop>\n### 221 - 272 = answer{-51} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 514 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 122 = answer{150} ### <eop>\n### 181 - 314 = answer{", "answer": -133}
{"prompt": "### 120 - 519 = answer{-399} ### <eop>\n### 335 - 341 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 422 - 46 = answer{376} ### <eop>\n### 18 - 276 = answer{-258} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 238 = answer{-99} ### <eop>\n### 272 - 494 = answer{", "answer": -222}
{"prompt": "### 516 - 29 = answer{487} ### <eop>\n### 114 - 148 = answer{-34} ### <eop>\n### 465 - 469 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 430 - 225 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 424 - 179 = answer{245} ### <eop>\n### 7 - 200 = answer{", "answer": -193}
{"prompt": "### 181 - 43 = answer{138} ### <eop>\n### 237 - 372 = answer{-135} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 102 = answer{-8} ### <eop>\n### 68 - 175 = answer{-107} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 272 = answer{-14} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 120 = answer{", "answer": 138}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 197 = answer{143} ### <eop>\n### 79 - 66 = answer{13} ### <eop>\n### 86 - 310 = answer{-224} ### <eop>\n### 258 - 53 = answer{205} ### <eop>\n### 131 - 6 = answer{125} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 38 = answer{", "answer": 144}
{"prompt": "### 400 - 266 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 490 = answer{-3} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 327 = answer{-273} ### <eop>\n### 501 - 170 = answer{331} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 510 = answer{", "answer": -304}
{"prompt": "### 304 - 215 = answer{89} ### <eop>\n### 206 - 388 = answer{-182} ### <eop>\n### 8 - 306 = answer{-298} ### <eop>\n### 261 - 353 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 407 - 346 = answer{61} ### <eop>\n### 27 - 4 = answer{", "answer": 23}
{"prompt": "### 459 - 13 = answer{446} ### <eop>\n### 413 - 413 = answer{0} ### <eop>\n### 438 - 359 = answer{79} ### <eop>\n### 353 - 510 = answer{-157} ### <eop>\n### 101 - 280 = answer{-179} ### <eop>\n### 83 - 190 = answer{", "answer": -107}
{"prompt": "### 72 - 170 = answer{-98} ### <eop>\n### 143 - 418 = answer{-275} ### <eop>\n### 157 - 20 = answer{137} ### <eop>\n### 503 - 38 = answer{465} ### <eop>\n### 50 - 61 = answer{-11} ### <eop>\n### 136 - 297 = answer{", "answer": -161}
{"prompt": "### 266 - 469 = answer{-203} ### <eop>\n### 267 - 214 = answer{53} ### <eop>\n### 504 - 95 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 324 = answer{47} ### <eop>\n### 268 - 165 = answer{103} ### <eop>\n### 148 - 483 = answer{", "answer": -335}
{"prompt": "### 419 - 161 = answer{258} ### <eop>\n### 317 - 382 = answer{-65} ### <eop>\n### 209 - 355 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 214 - 331 = answer{-117} ### <eop>\n### 443 - 324 = answer{119} ### <eop>\n### 487 - 80 = answer{", "answer": 407}
{"prompt": "### 254 - 60 = answer{194} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 241 = answer{-176} ### <eop>\n### 139 - 121 = answer{18} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 1 = answer{73} ### <eop>\n### 81 - 129 = answer{-48} ### <eop>\n### 474 - 323 = answer{", "answer": 151}
{"prompt": "### 456 - 345 = answer{111} ### <eop>\n### 362 - 196 = answer{166} ### <eop>\n### 414 - 349 = answer{65} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 104 = answer{328} ### <eop>\n### 330 - 160 = answer{170} ### <eop>\n### 254 - 213 = answer{", "answer": 41}
{"prompt": "### 345 - 241 = answer{104} ### <eop>\n### 334 - 214 = answer{120} ### <eop>\n### 467 - 265 = answer{202} ### <eop>\n### 426 - 250 = answer{176} ### <eop>\n### 147 - 413 = answer{-266} ### <eop>\n### 167 - 439 = answer{", "answer": -272}
{"prompt": "### 30 - 475 = answer{-445} ### <eop>\n### 468 - 447 = answer{21} ### <eop>\n### 94 - 481 = answer{-387} ### <eop>\n### 497 - 503 = answer{-6} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 338 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 208 - 375 = answer{", "answer": -167}
{"prompt": "### 363 - 84 = answer{279} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 97 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 191 - 296 = answer{-105} ### <eop>\n### 97 - 235 = answer{-138} ### <eop>\n### 419 - 10 = answer{409} ### <eop>\n### 406 - 61 = answer{", "answer": 345}
{"prompt": "### 456 - 30 = answer{426} ### <eop>\n### 451 - 81 = answer{370} ### <eop>\n### 71 - 339 = answer{-268} ### <eop>\n### 67 - 290 = answer{-223} ### <eop>\n### 382 - 505 = answer{-123} ### <eop>\n### 489 - 472 = answer{", "answer": 17}
{"prompt": "### 311 - 500 = answer{-189} ### <eop>\n### 290 - 382 = answer{-92} ### <eop>\n### 298 - 411 = answer{-113} ### <eop>\n### 192 - 459 = answer{-267} ### <eop>\n### 285 - 18 = answer{267} ### <eop>\n### 158 - 105 = answer{", "answer": 53}
{"prompt": "### 5 - 431 = answer{-426} ### <eop>\n### 394 - 137 = answer{257} ### <eop>\n### 124 - 146 = answer{-22} ### <eop>\n### 38 - 400 = answer{-362} ### <eop>\n### 246 - 97 = answer{149} ### <eop>\n### 472 - 363 = answer{", "answer": 109}
{"prompt": "### 227 - 282 = answer{-55} ### <eop>\n### 309 - 242 = answer{67} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 34 - 268 = answer{-234} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 265 - 313 = answer{", "answer": -48}
{"prompt": "### 12 - 446 = answer{-434} ### <eop>\n### 188 - 259 = answer{-71} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 425 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 338 - 37 = answer{301} ### <eop>\n### 475 - 170 = answer{305} ### <eop>\n### 154 - 210 = answer{", "answer": -56}
{"prompt": "### 73 - 321 = answer{-248} ### <eop>\n### 176 - 428 = answer{-252} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 334 = answer{98} ### <eop>\n### 319 - 500 = answer{-181} ### <eop>\n### 432 - 122 = answer{310} ### <eop>\n### 457 - 441 = answer{", "answer": 16}
{"prompt": "### 340 - 67 = answer{273} ### <eop>\n### 73 - 102 = answer{-29} ### <eop>\n### 189 - 389 = answer{-200} ### <eop>\n### 74 - 343 = answer{-269} ### <eop>\n### 137 - 283 = answer{-146} ### <eop>\n### 28 - 246 = answer{", "answer": -218}
{"prompt": "### 263 - 155 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 499 - 442 = answer{57} ### <eop>\n### 1 - 506 = answer{-505} ### <eop>\n### 46 - 212 = answer{-166} ### <eop>\n### 404 - 296 = answer{108} ### <eop>\n### 387 - 409 = answer{", "answer": -22}
{"prompt": "### 182 - 453 = answer{-271} ### <eop>\n### 355 - 378 = answer{-23} ### <eop>\n### 486 - 352 = answer{134} ### <eop>\n### 163 - 87 = answer{76} ### <eop>\n### 49 - 108 = answer{-59} ### <eop>\n### 54 - 327 = answer{", "answer": -273}
{"prompt": "### 143 - 315 = answer{-172} ### <eop>\n### 182 - 184 = answer{-2} ### <eop>\n### 371 - 362 = answer{9} ### <eop>\n### 376 - 235 = answer{141} ### <eop>\n### 119 - 123 = answer{-4} ### <eop>\n### 306 - 222 = answer{", "answer": 84}
{"prompt": "### 151 - 42 = answer{109} ### <eop>\n### 479 - 492 = answer{-13} ### <eop>\n### 243 - 169 = answer{74} ### <eop>\n### 127 - 496 = answer{-369} ### <eop>\n### 492 - 57 = answer{435} ### <eop>\n### 344 - 236 = answer{", "answer": 108}
{"prompt": "### 365 - 518 = answer{-153} ### <eop>\n### 65 - 226 = answer{-161} ### <eop>\n### 289 - 349 = answer{-60} ### <eop>\n### 459 - 476 = answer{-17} ### <eop>\n### 132 - 339 = answer{-207} ### <eop>\n### 349 - 267 = answer{", "answer": 82}